<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ArrayOfLabeledArticle xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Gareth Bale: The 'Lazy loner' under fire at Real Madrid

By Andy West
Spanish football writer
Gareth Bale is under heavy fire in Spain today, unwittingly finding himself the biggest victim in the fall-out from Real Madrid's recent loss of form.
Los Blancos' 4-3 home defeat by Schalke on Tuesday, which nearly sent them tumbling out of the Champions League, was seen as the final straw and has led to an ugly power struggle between club president Florentino Perez and the country's most influential 
And Bale is, rather unfairly, being placed right in the middle of the battle.
What have they said?

Marca's 11 points about Gareth Bale
One anonymous team-mate commented on Bale: "He doesn't defend because he doesn't want to"
In a full-page question and answer style story in Friday's newspaper, written by senior reporter Enrique Ortego, Marca tear into Bale in a vicious attack, portraying him as a selfish and lazy loner who doesn't play for the team.
Starting off by saying that Bale often appears "absent, lost and identifying little with the cause," the article goes on to describe the Welshman as having made "apparently little effort to integrate with the group 20 months after his arrival."
His defensive efforts are particularly heavily criticised, with Ortego arguing that he should be more capable of carrying out defensive work considering he started his career as a full-back, and even alleging that Bale has been given a different defensiv
And Marca's online edition was even more savage on Friday morning, running additional articles arguing that Bale is in the worst form of his career and quoting an anonymous teammate as saying: "He doesn't defend because he doesn't want to."
Another story suggests that Carlo Ancelotti is considering dropping Bale ahead of the crucial Clasico trip to Barcelona next weekend, and the overall message is clear: Marca want Bale out.
Is the criticism fair?

Gareth Bale lies on the floor
Gareth Bale is struggling playing in an unfamiliar position under Carlo Ancelotti
Bale, it is perfectly true, has been struggling for form in recent weeks.
He has not scored or assisted a single goal in eight consecutive games, and has gone through long periods of many games without making a significant impact upon the action.
However, that is explained in large part by his unusual playing position in Carlo Ancelotti's unconvincing hybrid 4-4-2/4-3-3 formation which requires him to play as both a midfielder and a forward, with the result that he has struggled to fulfil either 
And it is also the case that Bale is by no means the only Real player struggling for form, with Los Blancos winning only eight of their 15 games in 2015 - which has seen them knocked out of the Copa del Rey, suffer a 4-0 derby humiliation at Atletico Mad
Following the midweek Champions League embarrassment against Schalke, however, which resulted in Real's players assaulted by a crescendo of whistles and jeers even though they had just progressed to the quarter-finals, a scapegoat was needed.
Marca have decided to make Bale the victim.
Why Bale?

Gareth Bale holds up a Real Madrid shirt with his name on with President Florentino Perez
Gareth Bale signed a £300,000 per week, six-year deal in September 2013 after sealing an £85.3m move from Tottenham Hotspur
The direct cause for Marca's brutal assassination of Bale was a hastily scheduled press conference held by Real president Perez on Thursday, during which he attacked that morning's Marca front page story claiming that Ancelotti would be sacked if the tea
Directly singling out Marca for criticism, Perez suggested that his team's recent troubles have largely been the media's fault and slamming their supposed "lies".
And now Perez is learning the dangers of taking on the media, who can always have the final word in any argument, because Marca have responded by aiming their ire squarely at the man who is widely perceived as Perez's personal favourite: Bale.
Bale Stats Comparison
Bale in La Liga
2014/15
2013/14
Appearances
23
27
Starts
23
24
Minutes Played
2013
2069
Goals Scored
10
15
Minutes Per Goal
201.3
137.93
Shots On Target
32
30
Shots Off Target
34
40
Shooting Accuracy
48.48
42.86
Shots To Goal Conversion Rate
15.15
21.43
Assists
5
12
Chances Created (inc assists)
34
41
Total Passes Made
672
735
Pass Accuracy
78.72
76.33
There have long been rumours that Ancelotti has been ordered by Perez to keep Bale in the starting line-up, and the under-fire president even made an illuminating gaffe during his press appearance on Thursday by saying: "When I signed Bale, " before quic
By attacking Bale, therefore, Marca are really intending to undermine Perez.
Rather than the player, the newspaper's major quarrel is with the president - and discrediting Bale is just a handy way of getting at him.
Does it matter?

Real Madrid fans celebrate
Will Real Madrid's fans turn on Wales' golden boy?
Marca is by far Spain's biggest-selling and most influential sports newspaper, dedicating page after page of their daily output to the latest goings-on at Real Madrid.
On Friday, as a typical example, no other club is even mentioned until page 14's report of last night's Europa League meeting between Villarreal and Sevilla.
It also has its own radio station and a vast online following, and therefore plays a key role in both reflecting and determining the mood and opinions of Real's famously fickle fans.
The last person to seriously get on the wrong side of the paper, for example, was Jose Mourinho, who endured an increasingly fraught relationship with the media during his final season with the club.
Although Mourinho's eventual departure from the Bernabeu was genuinely as close to 'mutual consent' as can ever be possible, Marca's anti-Mourinho stance (which continues to this day, with the paper gleefully leaping upon every Chelsea defeat) was instru
If Marca's problem with Gareth Bale becomes a long-term policy, Gareth Bale will have a big problem at Real Madrid.
What now?

Gareth Bale celebrates with his trademark heart celebration
Bale will be hoping that his trademark celebration is needed on Sunday
Unfortunately for Bale, Real are at home to Levante on Sunday night and manager Carlo Ancelotti - who has always publicly firmly backed the Welshman - must decide whether to leave the former Tottenham man in the starting eleven or take him out of the fir
With homegrown forward Jese Rodriguez itching for his first Bernabeu start in La Liga since returning from long-term injury, there is a natural alternative to Bale if Ancelotti wishes to defuse the situation.
But that would be perceived as bowing to media pressure, and stubborn president Perez is unlikely to be advocating such a bold decision to his embattled coach.
Bale, therefore, is likely to play, and have the opportunity to make his critics eat their words. It's no exaggeration to suggest it could prove to be one of the most significant games of his career.
</Article>
    <IsAboutSport>true</IsAboutSport>
    <Category>Football</Category>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Bayern Munich moved 14 points clear at the top of the Bundesliga as Robert Lewandowski scored twice to secure a sixth successive league win.
Thomas Muller curled in a superb opener against Werder Bremen before David Alaba floated home a free-kick at the end of the first half.
Santiago Garcia had a second-half cross shot tipped over by Bayern's debutant keeper Pepe Reina after the break.
But Lewandowski headed in a third goal before tapping in late on.
To complete a satisfying afternoon for Bayern coach Pep Guardiola, captain Philipp Lahm made his comeback as a late substitute after four months out with a broken ankle.
Guardiola's side - who reached the Champions League quarter-finals with a 7-0 demolition of Shakhtar Donetsk on Wednesday - have dropped just 11 points in their 25 Bundesliga matches this season.
They were too strong for mid-table Bremen even though Manuel Neuer, Holger Badstuber, Franck Ribery and Arjen Robben were rested.
Muller goes for the left
Thomas Muller's 12th Bundesliga goal of the season - scored against Werder Bremen - was the first with his left foot
Bremen made a decent fight of it in a second half that threatened to become over-physical when centre-back Sebastian Prodl reacted to Mehdi Benatia's challenge on Clemens Fritz by going in late on the Bayern man.
Reina, making his first competitive appearance since arriving from Liverpool last August, had to deal with Garcia's effort, while Philipp Bargfrede had a goal ruled out for the home side after Davie Selke was judged to have handled.
But the Spain keeper did not have to work too hard for his clean sheet, in a match delayed as ground staff fixed the netting in one of the goals.
Levin Oztunali's early volley was Bremen's only notable first-half effort, with Lewandowski's downward header pushed over by keeper Raphael Wolf at the other end before Muller struck.
The midfielder burst on to Lewandowski's pass and, after Wolf had dashed out to block his first effort, curled a lovely shot into the corner when the ball came back to him.
Alaba's free-kick, right on half-time, gave the home side too much to do and their spirited attempt at a fight-back was ended when Muller was sent clear by Jerome Boateng, and lifted the ball beyond Wolf for Lewandowski to head into an empty net.
Bayern, who are now 14 points clear of second-placed VfL Wolfsburg, finished in style, with Lewandowski and Muller combining to carve open Bremen's defence, and the Germany international rolling the ball across goal for the Pole to tap in his 13th league
</Article>
    <IsAboutSport>true</IsAboutSport>
    <Category>Football</Category>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Heather Watson beats Camila Giorgi at Indian Wells

British number one Heather Watson withstood a storming fightback from Camila Giorgi to reach the third round in Indian Wells for the first time.
Watson, 22, looked on course for a straightforward win at 5-0 in the second set, only for the Italian 29th seed to win five straight games.
The Briton held her nerve, however, and sealed a 7-5 7-5 victory with her sixth break of serve in the match.
Watson goes on to face seventh seed Agnieszka Radwanska in the last 32.
"It was a very tough match as I knew it would be," said Watson. "Camila's a great player and she's shot up the rankings this past year."
Giorgi, ranked 10 places higher than Watson at 33 in the world, hit 18 double faults and 54 unforced errors in a wildly inconsistent performance.
The Italian twice went a break up in the first set but the constant flow of double faults allowed Watson to recover each time, and ultimately take it in the 12th game.
Watson was in total command as she reeled off 11 consecutive points early in the second and made it seven games in a row to lead 5-0.
Agnieszka Radwanska of Poland
Radwanska has won all three previous matches against Watson, most recently in Indian Wells last year
With the match all but gone and the pressure off, Giorgi suddenly found her game and hauled her way back against an increasingly edgy Watson.
The Guernsey-born player was under huge pressure at 5-5, 30-30, but found an ace at the crucial moment and then broke for the sixth time to seal the win.
"I didn't feel I did much wrong [in the second set], she played too good, hitting winners and aces. I just had to stay tough and keep fighting," added Watson.
"I feel that I'm playing better and better as each match goes on and hopefully I can play even better in my next match."
Poland's Radwanska beat American Alison Riske 6-3 6-1, while Romanian third seed Simona Halep overcame Russian's Daria Gavrilova 2-6 6-1 6-2.
Andy Murray will take on Canada's Vasek Pospisil in the first round of the singles and he made an impressive start to the doubles.
Partnering 18-year-old Australian Thanasi Kokkinakis, the British number one enjoyed a 6-3 7-5 win over fourth seeds Jean-Julien Rojer and Horia Tecau.
</Article>
    <IsAboutSport>true</IsAboutSport>
    <Category>Tennis</Category>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Serena Williams ends 14-year Indian Wells boycott with win

Serena Williams ended a 14-year boycott of Indian Wells with a 7-5 7-5 win over Monica Niculescu on her return to the California tournament.
Williams was booed and heckled during her last appearance at the event in 2001, when she won the final.
This time she was given a standing ovation as she walked on to court, before sealing victory in two hours.
"It is one of the biggest moments of my career," said the 33-year-old. "I feel like I've already won this tournament."
The American was watched by several family members, including her mother, as she returned to the scene of her 2001 defeat of Belgian Kim Clijsters.
That final was marred by the behaviour of some fans who heckled her and her family, apparently in response to sister Venus withdrawing injured from the semi-final between the siblings.
Serena Williams at Indian wells
Williams had played 651 matches and won 55 WTA titles since she last competed at Indian Wells in 2001. On her three previous appearances in the main draw, from 1999 to 2001, she had a 14-1 record that included titles in 1999 and 2001 and a quarter-final 
Her father, Richard, later accused fans of racial abuse and the Williams sisters had not returned to the event until Serena's match on Friday, with Venus still staying away.
"I felt like I made the right decision and I knew I wanted to do it," said Serena.
The world number one, top seed for the event, initially looked nervous against her Romanian opponent and made 48 unforced errors before eventually winning a lengthy and hard-fought match.
"I didn't know what to expect," Williams said of the standing ovation.
"In the last couple of moments leading up to it, I was focused on warming up for the match and I wasn't really prepared for that. I was overwhelmed by it.
"It was such a warm feeling. It made me feel incredibly well. And receiving the love from the crowd here, it really meant a lot to me."
Serena Williams
Williams was close to tears as she walked on to court at Indian Wells for the first time since beating Kim Clijsters in the 2001 final
Serena Williams
"It felt great walking out here and everyone wishing me well," said Williams, after receiving a warm reception
Serna Williams
Williams has won 55 titles since last playing at Indian Wells - including 18 of her 19 Grand Slams - but she said this win ranked "super high" on her all-time list
</Article>
    <IsAboutSport>true</IsAboutSport>
    <Category>Tennis</Category>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Roger Federer beats Novak Djokovic to win Dubai title

Roger Federer beat world number one Novak Djokovic 6-3 7-5 to win his seventh Dubai Championship title.
The Swiss, playing in his 126th ATP final, served brilliantly throughout to trouble Djokovic and also pass 9,000 aces in singles matches.
But the Serb hung on and he had set points in the second set only for Federer to rescue the situation.
The world number two saved all seven break points against him and another superb serve set up the win.
"Playing against Novak is always special. I think we get the best out of each other," Federer said.
"I definitely won the big points tonight so I am pleased I came up with some good serves."
Federer was in trouble when he had to save break points at 1-1 in the opening set but he got through that test and from then on started to take the ball early to put the pressure on Djokovic.
Federer facts
Federer now leads his head-to-head meetings with Djokovic 20-17
It was their fourth meeting in Dubai - Federer is 3-1 ahead
Federer's previous Dubai final wins had come against Jiri Novak (2003), Feliciano Lopez ('04), Ivan Ljubicic ('05), Mikhail Youzhny ('07), Andy Murray ('12) and Tomas Berdych ('14)
Federer's win means eight ATP World Tour tournaments in 2015 have been won by over-30s
When another backhand gave Federer a chance of a break, he took it to make it 5-3 and then served out the set, sealing it with a service winner.
The second set proved equally tight but it was the Federer serve which was put under pressure first at 3-4 with a well-placed Djokovic forehand giving him two break points.
However, the world number two responded with four tremendous serves in a row to level the match again and he then had to use his serve to help get him out of trouble at 4-5 when Djokovic had two set points.
Novak Djokovic
Djokovic was beaten for only the second time this season and the first time in five Dubai finals
A Djokovic double fault gave Federer break points of his own at 5-5 and the defending champion drove his advantage home with a forehand winner to edge ahead.
It left Federer serving for the match and although he had a brief wobble when he netted on his first match point, he made no mistake with his second.
"I thought it was a good match. I thought there wasn't much difference, a few points decided the winner," said Djokovic.
"If you don't use these opportunities against Roger, then he fires back. But I didn't play too bad."
</Article>
    <IsAboutSport>true</IsAboutSport>
    <Category>Tennis</Category>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>European Indoors: Jenny Meadows pulls out of 800m final

Britain's Jenny Meadows will not compete in Sunday's 800m final at the European Championships in Prague after withdrawing on "medical grounds".
British Athletics said a virus the 33-year-old had been suffering with all week had worsened overnight.
"I'm disappointed not to be running. I went to bed hopeful that I could compete," said the Wigan athlete.
Meadows, the 2011 800m champion, qualified for the final after Russia's Anastasiya Bazdyreva was disqualified.
The Briton had been in the form of her life before the championships, posting four of the five quickest times of the year over the distance indoors.
She had failed to qualify automatically for the final, finishing a disappointing fourth, but a successful British Athletics appeal against the Russian athlete who had stepped off the track ensured her progress.
"I would have given everything I have got in me over those four laps but I am serious about doing well in the outdoor season this year and that has to be the bigger picture," added Meadows.
Meadows was only awarded her 2011 indoor title 15 months after the event when original winner Yevgeniya Zinurova, of Russia, was banned for doping.
But after returning to top the world rankings this season after three injury-hit years, Meadows admitted: "I just feel like having a bit of a cry and thinking when will life ever turn for me."
Switzerland's Selina Buchel won the event and Meadows later tweeted:  "Gutted not to have taken my opportunity in the 800m final today but glad to see an athlete who hasn't served a doping ban or anyone implicated to have doped win! Buchel ran a gutsy ra
</Article>
    <IsAboutSport>true</IsAboutSport>
    <Category>Athletics</Category>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Vanuatu president calls for help after cyclone destruction
Destruction caused by Cyclone Pam in Vanuatu, 14 March 2015
Many residents are spending a second night in emergency shelters
Continue reading the main story
Related Stories

Cyclone Olwyn hits WA coastline
Vanuatu country profile
Vanuatu's President Baldwin Lonsdale has called for international help after Cyclone Pam ripped through the Pacific archipelago.

Describing it as a "calamity", he said he spoke with a "heavy heart".

Aid agencies say the cyclone, which veered off its expected course on Saturday and struck populated areas, has caused "complete devastation".

Save the Children says eight people are confirmed dead but it is feared dozens more may have been killed.

Located about a quarter of the way from Australia to Hawaii, Vanuatu has a population of 267,000 spread over 65 islands. About 47,000 people live in the capital, Port Vila.

Many residents there are spending a second night in emergency shelters after finding their homes destroyed.

The UN's Office for the Co-ordination for Humanitarian Assistance (UNOCHA) described the storm, which brought winds of up to 270km/h (170mph) and torrential rain, as "extremely destructive".

"A disaster of this magnitude has not been experienced by Vanuatu in recent history - particularly in terms of the reach of the potential damage and the ferocity of the storm," said Sune Gudnitz, head of the agency's Pacific office.

Jump media playerMedia player helpOut of media player. Press enter to return or tab to continue.
Phil Mercer reports on Cyclone Pam which has ravaged the Pacific nation of Vanuatu. Video courtesy of YouTube/Isso Nihmei at 350.org
President Lonsdale was speaking in Japan at the UN's World Conference on Disaster Risk and Reduction.

"I stand to appeal on behalf of the government and the people of Vanuatu that the global community give a lending hand in responding to these very current calamities... that have struck us," he said.

Vulnerable islands
Chloe Morrison, an emergency communications officer with World Vision who is in Port Vila, said on Saturday that streets were littered with roofing, uprooted trees and toppled power lines.

There were reports of entire villages in remote areas being destroyed, she said.

"The damage is quite extensive in Port Vila but there are so many more vulnerable islands. I can't even imagine what it's like in those vulnerable communities.''

Devastation caused by Cyclone Pam in Vanuatu, 14 March 2015
A complete picture of the destruction has yet to emerge
Cyclone Pam batters Port Vila, Vanuatu. 14 March 2015
The cyclone whipped up huge waves to batter the coasts of the archipelago
Storm damage in Port Vila, Vanuatu. 14 March 2015
Many trees were felled, and houses had their roofs torn off
A priority was to make sure residents had shelter and enough food and drinking water.

The extent of the devastation was unlikely to be known for several days, said Tom Skirrow, Save the Children's Vanuatu country director.

Unicef spokeswoman Alice Clements described the cyclone as "15-30 minutes of absolute terror" as it passed over Port Vila.

"I saw the sliding doors from my three-storey-hotel room completely blow away - it was terrifying," she said.

Unicef in New Zealand warned that Cyclone Pam could be one of the worst ever weather disasters for the region.

"While it is too early to say for certain, early reports are indicating that this weather disaster could potentially be one of the worst in Pacific history," New Zealand executive director Vivien Maidaborn said in a statement.

Unconfirmed reports said that 44 people had died in Penama province in the north-east of Vanuatu, the UNOCHA said earlier in a statement.

Storm damage in Port Vila, Vanuatu. 14 March 2015
Residents in Vanuatu emerged from their shelters on Saturday to take stock of the damage
Storm damage in Port Vila, Vanuatu. 14 March 2015
Boats moored in Port Vila bore the brunt of the storm
Australia says it is preparing to send a crisis response team to Vanuatu if needed. New Zealand pledged NZ$1m (£500,000), the EU promised ?1m (£710,000), and the UK said it would give up to £2m in aid.

All six provinces of Vanuatu were under red alert, meaning people are advised to immediately seek shelter.

Pam, a category five tropical storm, had already caused major damage on other Pacific islands, including Kiribati and the Solomon Islands.

Tuvalu, a group of nine tiny islands north-east of Vanuatu, has also declared a state of emergency after the cyclone caused flash floods there.
</Article>
    <IsAboutSport>false</IsAboutSport>
    <Category>NoSport</Category>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Pope Francis hints at 'brief' papacy
Pope Francis meets Pope emeritus Benedict XVI in Castel Gandolfo on 23 March 2013
Pope Francis praised Pope Benedict's decision to resign in 2013
Continue reading the main story
Related Stories

Profile: Pope Francis
Francis: The Pope's calling
90 secs: Pope Francis's style Watch
Pope Francis has suggested he may resign his papacy like his predecessor, rather than remain at the Vatican for life.

The pontiff made the comments during a interview with Mexican television, marking the second anniversary of his election.

"I have the feeling that my pontificate will be brief. Four or five years; I do not know, even two or three," he said.

He praised Pope Benedict's decision to step aside in 2013 as "courageous".

"Benedict should not be considered an exception, but an institution. Maybe he will be the only one for a long time, maybe he will not be the only one.

"But an institutional door has been opened," he told the Televisa channel.

Pope Francis has hinted in the past that he could retire, but said he was opposed to the idea of an age limit for leaders of the Catholic Church.

"To say that one is in charge up to 80 years, creates a sensation that the pontificate is at its end and that would not be a good thing," he added.

Pope Francis receiving a gift of a special pizza during his weekly general audience in Saint Peter's Square, Vatican City, 11 March 2015
The pontiff revealed he missed being able to do simple things like visiting a pizzeria without being noticed
A papal conclave elected Pope Francis as Benedict XVI's successor on 13 March 2013. He became the first Latin American to lead the Church.

During the interview he admitted he was "surprised" by the decision and had only carried a small suitcase to Rome, with the expectation he would return to Buenos Aires.

line
Analysis: James Reynolds, BBC News, Rome

Reporters have asked Pope Francis on at least three occasions whether or not he intends to follow his predecessor Benedict XVI in retiring. On each occasion, the Pope has answered with roughly the same words.

"I think that a Pope emeritus should not be an exception," he told reporters in August 2014, "You can ask me: 'What if one day you don't feel prepared to go on?' I would do the same, I would do the same!"

But the Pope also makes it clear that he will stay in the job as long as he has the physical strength to do so. His interview with Mexican TV makes it clear that he still enjoys his papacy.

"Do you like being Pope?" the reporter asked. "It doesn't displease me!" the Pope replied.

line
His simple style has won him praise from Catholics, as have his promises to reform the Curia - the Church's internal government.

However, he said two years of his papacy had now passed and he felt it would not continue for very much longer.

"I do not know. But I feel that the Lord has placed me here for a short time, and nothing more," he added.

"But it is a feeling. I always leave the possibility open."

He told Televisa that he "did not mind being Pope", but missed the anonymity associated with life as a priest.

"The only thing I would like is to go out one day, without being recognised, and go to a pizzeria for a pizza."
</Article>
    <IsAboutSport>false</IsAboutSport>
    <Category>NoSport</Category>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Chilean authorities have declared a state of emergency as a raging forest fire forced thousands of people to flee their homes.

The fire is threatening the port cities of Valparaiso and Vina del Mar.

The interior ministry said about 4,500 people had already been evacuated and another 10,000 might need to be moved.

Valparaiso is still recovering from a forest fire last April that killed 15 people, injured more than 500 and destroyed nearly 3,000 homes.

The fire began at an illegal garbage dump on Friday afternoon, officials said, and spread quickly fanned by strong winds.

Smoke billows over Valparaiso, Chile. 14 March 2015
A huge pall of smoke from the forest fire was hanging over the Pacific port city of Valparaiso
By late Friday, Chile's Emergency Office estimated that about 300 hectares (740 acres) had been affected.

Emergency crews battled through the night to keep the flames from reaching residential districts in Valparaiso.

Three firefighters have been injured so far and a 67-year-old woman died of cardio-respiratory causes, the interior ministry said.

Valparaiso's poorest areas, often made up of little more than wooden huts, were worst hit by last year's devastating fire.

Entire neighbourhoods were razed and many of those who died were found in the burned-down homes they had refused to leave.
</Article>
    <IsAboutSport>false</IsAboutSport>
    <Category>NoSport</Category>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>SHARAPOVA ON SERENA: SHE'S THE BEST
Serena Williams' return to Indian Wells has been one of the most positive stories of the year - and her chief rival, World No.2 Maria Sharapova, is as excited as anyone.
Published March 14, 2015 12:13

Embed

INDIAN WELLS, CA, USA - Serena Williams' return to Indian Wells has been one of the most positive stories of the year so far, and while that may mean the rest of the field's chances of winning the BNP Paribas Open title are smaller now, their joy to have

And no player is more excited to have the World No.1 back than the World No.2, Maria Sharapova.

"I think it's all positive," Sharapova said in her All Access Hour interview this week.

"It's a great decision. It's great for the tour. It's great for tennis in general. I've always said that when you're playing any tournament, and especially being at the top of tennis, you want to be playing against the best. And as I've said before, she'

Though it's been a while since Sharapova has beaten Williams, she's pushed many of their matches very close, including a very tight two-setter in the final of the Australian Open this past January.

She's got a lot of respect for her longtime rival - what does she admire the most about her?

"I admire the fact that even though she's achieved everything she has, that she still has the passion and desire to keep getting better," Sharapova said. "From a woman's perspective, at one point when you've achieved so much and you're so good at what yo

Sharapova - like Williams a two-time champion at Indian Wells - will be playing for the first time since withdrawing before her semifinal match in Acapulco a few weeks ago due to a GI illness.

"It took a little bit longer than I expected to get better," Sharapova said. "I got home and had to take a little bit of time off. It was unfortunate. You never know when you're going to get that type of thing. But it was good to get rid of it, get my en

And there was one more very important piece of business to discuss - how Dolce, her dog, is doing.

"I think he likes it here! He likes it better than the Miami humidity," Sharapova said.

"It's better for his hair here."
</Article>
    <IsAboutSport>true</IsAboutSport>
    <Category>Tennis</Category>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>NICULESCU EARNS SERENA'S RESPECT
Monica Niculescu may have come out on the losing side of Friday night's clash with Serena Williams, but she has done her reputation no harm whatsoever.
Published March 13, 2015 12:14

Niculescu Earns Serena's Respect Monica Niculescu
INDIAN WELLS, CA, USA - They walked onto court as two players who had never faced each other in singles play. But after Serena Williams ground out a 7-5, 7-5 victory, Monica Niculescu and the current Road To Singapore leader exited the court Friday night

On the surface, Niculsecu appeared poised to play the role of bit player in Williams' larger saga: Her return to the BNP Paribas Open after a 14-year absence. On an emotional night, the 13-year pro from Romania used past experience to put the situation i

Of course, as most players eventually discover, bringing your best is not enough to defeat Williams, but Niculescu certainly earned respect.

How did the No.68th-ranked player learn to play with such steely nerve?

"I played also one time on a big court in China against Li Na," Niculescu said. "They had a big court for her and it was the same; I felt amazing when I walked on the court - but that match I won!"

Niculescu faced Li in the 2011 China Open and swept to a 6-4, 6-0 victory in front a stunned and adoring Chinese crowd.

"But it was almost the same because the people were expecting Li to play well and they made that court just for her and so many people and yeah, it was a different result against Williams," she added. "But I felt good. The crowd helped me also and they w

Niculescu's game exceeded expectations as her soft touch and use of spin challenged Williams' movement and return skills. Niculescu entered the match with a 2-5 record in 2015. However, she has hoisted a pair of WTA trophies thanks to victories in 2013 a

Despite Niculescu's low profile, Williams was well aware of her finesse skill set.

"I know her game - I think everyone in the locker room knows her game," Williams said. "But gosh, it was interesting. I just never got the same ball and I got that forehand a few times and it was low, it was high and then it was just I wasn't able to get

Tricky for so many. Niculescu provided enough resistance and entertainment to exit with her pride intact. The crowd received an entertaining match and their champion once again proved her amazing ability to shine in tense moments.

In the end, Niculescu earned a way into Williams' career memory bank.

"The match falls super-high up. Definitely up there. Really close, probably the best," Williams said. "It's interesting to say that I feel like I've already won the trophy. I feel I don't actually have to hold the trophy at the end of this tournament. I 
</Article>
    <IsAboutSport>true</IsAboutSport>
    <Category>Tennis</Category>
  </LabeledArticle>
</ArrayOfLabeledArticle>