<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ArrayOfLabeledArticle xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Veronika Petra-Goodnight was working as a financial assistant at a university when she first fell in love with hula hooping.

She was enchanted by a performer’s tricks, twists and turns and decided to try it at home. Within the first month, Petra-Goodnight hula hooped so frequently that it gave her a hernia.

She pressed on, challenging herself with new tricks, including twirling a hoop engulfed in flames. She began teaching workshops as she advanced her craft. After getting voted fire hooper of the year by online group Hooping.org, Petra-Goodnight started receiving phone calls from talent agencies.

More attention — and success — followed. She appeared in Britney Spears’ Circus music video, she travelled to Beirut with Cirque USA and went to London with Cirque Du Soleil.

 “When I resigned my job, I left a note that read, ‘I am quitting to run away with the circus,’ then I ate fire at my going-away party,” said Petra-Goodnight, who has been performing as a profession since 2007.

It might sound glamorous — and for some it is. But behind the scenes, the circus business isn’t always as exciting as tumbling across elephants in feather headdresses, juggling on a unicycle or swinging across the sky on a mile-high trapeze.

Some performers say they have made tough lifestyle choices: leaving a marriage, forgoing health insurance despite high risk of major injury and living out of tiny trailers in venue parking lots.

Still, those who have run away with the circus say the adrenaline rush of a post-performance standing ovation, the chance to travel the world and family-like relationships with everyone (and everything) from contortionists to zebras can make it worthwhile.

Navigating the ropes

The path of a circus performer is often similar to that of a touring theatre actor’s career. In other words, it’s tough. There are the dynamics of life on the road, fierce competition to secure limited and temporary contracts, constant self-promotion and auditions before directors who seem to specialise in harsh opinions. Added to that, Petra-Goodnight and others say, performers must be physically fit at all times. They must also continually sharpen and enhance their skills to remain competitive, especially if they didn’t go to circus school.

Rex Camphuis, co-founding executive director of Cirque School LA said he estimates about 50% of performers go to a specialised circus school, where training lasts two to four years and a bachelor’s degree in circus arts is attainable. In Australia, for instance, a degree might cost $13,000 for locals ($10,000) and $21,550 ($16,578) for international students, according to the National Institute of Circus Arts Australia. But schooling alone doesn’t necessarily land you a circus job, since producers don’t typically care about credentials. Instead, they focus on auditions.

 “You have to find time to train, to feed your body right, to tune your performances and make sure they’re appropriate for who has hired you, and at the same time, maintain who you are and your personal life,” Petra-Goodnight said.

And you’ll be doing it on a limited budget. The circus life doesn’t exactly pay well for most.

Glam life, unglamorous pay

Camphuis estimates a performer can make anywhere from $200 to $3,500 for a single performance. Rates, he said, can drop to $50 to $250 per show if someone performs every day while on tour. And pay varies wildly from year to year. Petra-Goodnight said she could make $10,000 in a month, then not make more than $10, 000 in a year.

Expenses also add up.

Frequent travel may be fun, but performers often pay their own way. In many cases, they must also supply their own equipment and costumes.

Rebecca Ostroff, 58, who dangles by her teeth and spins from a swinging apparatus for US-based Kelly Miller Circus might spend $300 on rhinestones for a costume and the same for a headdress. She also goes through about several cases of dental floss per year, which she uses to re-sew jewels onto her costumes that fall off during vigorous use.

Having health insurance is also a necessary expense, especially since an injury or poor health could cost you your career. In 2014, tumbler and trapeze artist Jeannemarie Van Zeyl tore her rotator cuff during a trapeze act and she hasn’t returned to performing. She’s also suffered concussions. Many performers say injuries come with the territory, especially when they create new, limit-pushing acts.

Securing work

Many performers develop an original act with extreme feats like juggling chainsaws or maybe an unusual twist like training goats to jump through hoops. The act generates buzz and interest, making it easier to land gigs through word of mouth.

For instance, Ostroff’s “Iron Jaw” act won her a performance in the 2011 circus film Water for Elephants. Ostroff said she has performed her routine about 500 times a year for the last 27 years and has also worked as a ringmaster.

While less common, some acts are represented by agencies such as the international Circus Stardust Entertainment, said Jack Marsh, creative director of American Circus Flora. Other times, acts are scouted, much like professional athletes.

Marsh said he frequents shows and festivals, including the Montreal Completement Cirque, to scout acts from places as diverse as Cuba, Kazakhstan and Finland. He also receives upwards of 200 videos a year from prospective performers.

Some big-name circuses such as Cirque du Soleil post job opportunities on their websites, while other circuses, including Ringling Brothers Barnum and Bailey, post listings on popular job boards like Careerbuilder.com.

Acts get locked in by a circus well in advance, especially if the performer doesn’t have a work visa in the production’s native country.

Out of balance

The stress of circus life can be a difficult balance for someone who wants a home and family.

While Van Zeyl loves circus performance, she also craves the normalcy of everyday life.

“If you want to be full-fledged, you have to be completely devoted — not have a cat, own a house, or be in love,” said Van Zeyl. “But I have a mortgage to pay and got married a year ago. I think those are things you have to weigh out.”

She has made trade-offs to create work-life balance, including performing in small, local productions and rounding out her income by teaching tumbling. It helps that she lives about 100km outside of Los Angeles: a hub for music video and television gigs that can be had through recruitment agencies like LA Circus that cast performers locally.

Meanwhile Ostroff, whose husband is a trumpet player in the circus band, home schools her daughter while on the road and argues circus life isn’t all that different than life in any two-income home.

“It’s just like you live in a town and you have your house and your job or school and you do your things except you’re in a circus, so your house just happens to change locations,” Ostroff said.

Regardless, most performers say they wouldn’t trade circus life for workaday. When Petra-Goodnight thinks she’s seen it all, over and over again she is surprised. Recently, she went to a Cirque Dreams performance where she saw a Romanian family perform a jaw-dropping tumbling act and an Armenian couple do contortionist moves while spinning on roller skates.

“I thought, at any second he could lose her hand and she would go flying. When you see those type of circus performers, it’s mindboggling,” Petra-Goodnight said. “Then you see something in [audience members] spark when they go to shows like this and it is so cool to witness.”</Article>
    <Category>NoSport</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Kompany: Huge difference between City and Barça, Bayern
(PA) Thursday 19 March 2015
Share
2
Kompany: Huge difference between City and Barça, Bayern
© Getty Images
Manchester City captain Vincent Kompany accepts the club still remain a long way short of fulfilling their European dreams. The gap between City and the continent's best clubs was starkly illustrated on Wednesday, when Barcelona dumped the English champions out of the UEFA Champions League with a commanding performance at Camp Nou.

Thanks to the brilliance of Joe Hart, City at least kept the scoreline respectable - losing 1-0 for a 3-1 aggregate defeat - but they were distinctly second best to a Barça side inspired by the magnificent Lionel Messi. City may have made considerable progress in the seven years since their Abu Dhabi takeover, but the journey still has a long way to go.

Kompany said: "The reality is they were a better team, there is no shame in admitting that. For me there is a big, big difference. I will just mention Bayern Munich and Barcelona, and then there are the rest of the teams, with Real Madrid probably in between.

"Ultimately we have always said our goal is to become as good as them, but it will take some time. They are really good.

"Bayern Munich and Barcelona are not just Champions League-winning teams, they are World Cup-winning teams as well. They have generations that have played together a long time.

"Of course we want to make up the gap but you just have to be true to yourself. We have the ambition to be as good as they are one day, but it is not going to happen overnight."

There is a big, big difference. I will just mention Bayern Munich and Barcelona, and then there are the rest of the teams, with Real Madrid probably in between.Vincent Kompany
City's exit meant that England will not have a representative in the quarter-finals of the Champions League for the second time in three seasons.

"The gap will eventually get closer," said Kompany. "Whether it is Arsenal, Chelsea, [Manchester] United, the gap will become closer and I just hope it is us that gets there the first."

'Phenomenal' Hart
City were outplayed in the first leg at the Etihad Stadium three weeks ago, but had hoped Hart's late penalty save, which kept the score 2-1, might have proved the tie's turning point. It proved anything but as Barcelona dominated from the outset, hitting the post within moments through Neymar. Messi was at his inspirational best, setting up Ivan Rakitic's 31st-minute goal and generally running City ragged.

It was remarkable the scoreline stayed at 1-0, with Luis Suarez also hitting the woodwork twice and England goalkeeper Hart producing a series of stunning saves in one of the best performances of his career. City might have made the latter stages interesting had Sergio Aguero not had a penalty saved by Marc-Andre ter Stegen, but they could complain little about the result.

Asked about Hart's display, Kompany said: "It was phenomenal. On that side of the pitch I felt we had all the luck we needed to get a result.

"It was probably just the penalty - if we had scored a goal it could have been a different game. It would have been a great way to get back into the tie, and it would have been interesting to see what the last 15 minutes would have been like back at 1-1.

"If you want to win against those teams you need a very special performance and a little bit of luck on your side. Then you can beat them, but every team can lose. There is no shame."

Kompany demands strong finish
Despite progress always seeming unlikely, the defeat is another blow to City's morale after an indifferent spell in the Premier League. Having fallen six points behind Chelsea, who have a game in hand, it now seems unlikely City can retain their title and their season is in danger of fizzling out. They could even face a battle to hold on to second place as the likes of Arsenal, Liverpool and Manchester United gear up for a strong finish. Kompany is determined to ensure that does not happen.

The 28-year-old said: "Forget about Chelsea. We owe it to ourselves, to our fans to have a good end to this campaign. Then again, if we finish this campaign as good as we can, maybe there is still something in it. We will have to see. It is not in our hands by any means, but we just have to go back and work hard and improve."</Article>
    <Category>Football</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>MARIA SHARAPOVA: DRIVEN TO SUCCEED
Maria Sharapova has crammed a lot into her time as Porsche brand ambassador, juggling her tennis commitments with advertising shoots, car design and chauffer-driven rides with Formula 1 drivers.
Published March 18, 2015 12:12

Maria Sharapova: Driven To Succeed Maria Sharapova
Two years ago, Maria Sharapova added German sports car manufacturer Porsche to her ever-growing list of endorsement contracts.

Porsche hand-picked Sharapova to head up its global communications campaign, and she has thrown herself into the role with gusto. The Russian has crammed a lot into her time as brand ambassador, juggling her tennis globe-trotting with advertising shoots, car design and chauffeur-driven rides with Formula 1 drivers.

In a blog for luxury lifestyle publication Haute Living, Sharapova looks back on her favorite moments from an action-packed journey, which begin, aptly enough, at the Porsche Tennis Grand Prix in Stuttgart. The Russian was no stranger to the automobile behemoth, having taken home a 911 Carrera S Cabriolet after winning the previous year's tournament, and to the delight of all parties - save for beaten finalist Li Na - she defended her title in style.

Porsche's long-term relationship with tennis has made it an ideal fit in the Sharapova sponsorship portfolio, and she has used the ambassadorial platform to not only promote the sport but also the modern woman.

"One of the things I've loved most is the opportunity to help Porsche expand its brand message to women - sports cars aren't just for men! I jumped at the chance to represent the modern woman: a woman with a successful career and a myriad of passions, a woman who treats herself to luxury, and most of all, a woman who likes to drive her own life," Sharapova told Haute Living readers.

There have also been plenty of perks to the gig. One such moment came at last year's Winter Olympics in the Russian's hometown of Sochi, where she unveiled a car with a difference: The Panamera GTS 'by Maria Sharapova'.</Article>
    <Category>Tennis</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Five things to watch when Blackhawks face Rangers
Wednesday, 03.18.2015 / 3:00 AM / NHL Insider
By Brian Compton - NHL.com Deputy Managing Editor
CommentPrintE-mail
It may very well be a preview of the Stanley Cup Final when the New York Rangers host the Chicago Blackhawks at Madison Square Garden. This week's Wednesday Night Rivalry game (8 p.m. ET; NBCSN, TVA, SN1) features two of the top teams in the NHL, each of which seems primed to play deep into the spring.

With the Rangers atop the League standings and the Blackhawks battling for position in the Central Division, there's plenty at stake for each team.

Here are five things to watch between the Rangers and Blackhawks:


WEDNESDAY NIGHT RIVALRY
The Chicago Blackhawks visit the New York Rangers at 8 p.m. ET in the early game of a Wednesday Night Rivalry doubleheader. In the late game, the Los Angeles Kings continue their playoff push against the Anaheim Ducks at 10:30 p.m. ET.
Hawks vs. Rangers video | Kings vs. Ducks video
X-Factors: Saad, Talbot video | Toffoli, Lindholm video
Hawks-Rangers storylines | Tale of the Tape
Closer look: CHI, NYR play fast | Weekes
Richards eyes Cup | Lundqvist injury update
Kopitar, Gabby want more | Williams on push
video Join the Twitter conversation: #RivalryNight
1. Who replaces St. Louis?
The Rangers recently lost defenseman Kevin Klein for 3-4 weeks because of an upper-body injury, and now they'll be without forward Martin St. Louis, who sustained a lower-body injury late in a 2-1 win against the Florida Panthers on Sunday.

St. Louis, who has 47 points (20 goals, 27 assists) in 68 games, is expected to miss 10-14 days.

Rangers left wing Tanner Glass missed the game Sunday because of upper-body soreness, but is expected to play against the Blackhawks. That would give New York 12 healthy forwards.

2. Blackhawks' power play clicking again

Prior to its back-to-back road wins, Chicago struggled with the man-advantage, going 1-for-16 in its previous six games. But the Blackhawks scored four power-play goals in 11 opportunities in wins against the Arizona Coyotes and San Jose Sharks. Defenseman Duncan Keith and forward Patrick Sharp scored on the power play against the Sharks on Saturday.

"It's nice to have some relief across the board in those areas definitely," Sharp, who ended a 19-game goal drought, told the Blackhawks website. "Power play, penalty kill … those things are going to be up and down all season long. You try to make them as consistent as possible, but there's certainly peaks and valleys. We can gain some confidence knowing that we scored a couple of goals on the power play in both games and we know how valuable both specials teams are going to be going down the stretch."

3. All eyes on Talbot

Rangers fans probably would have settled for .500 hockey when they learned No. 1 goalie Henrik Lundqvist would miss a substantial amount of time because of a vascular injury. But New York hasn't missed a beat thanks to the play of Cam Talbot.

Talbot was named the NHL's Second Star of the week on Monday after going 3-0-0 with a 1.00 GAA and a .969 save percentage, helping the Rangers extend their win streak to five games. Talbot made 38 saves in a 2-1 victory against the Florida Panthers on Sunday.

"It didn't surprise anybody in here, to be honest," Rangers defenseman Marc Staal said. "Obviously you don't want to see what happened to [Lundqvist] happen, but we're excited for him to get an opportunity to show what he's got on a consistent basis. He's been very good for us as a backup. It's his time to shine."

Lundqvist was cleared to practice on Tuesday, which means the number of starts Talbot receives down the stretch will likely decrease dramatically. But there's no denying how much he's meant to the Rangers during the past six weeks.

4. Who's in goal for Blackhawks?


Scott Darling

SCOTT DARLING
GOALIE - CHI
RECORD: 6-3-0
GAA: 2.18 | SVP: .930
Chicago coach Joel Quenneville opted to start No. 1 goalie Corey Crawford against the New York Islanders at United Center on Tuesday. Will Crawford will play against the Rangers with such a quick turnaround.
If Crawford does not play, the Blackhawks would start Scott Darling, who has a 2.18 GAA and a .930 save percentage in nine games with Chicago this season.

"Big games, we'll see," Quenneville said.

Quenneville added it would be "under discussion" regarding starting Crawford again Wednesday.

5. Rangers shuffle lines

New York's top line will have a different look against the Blackhawks. Seeking more production from some of his top forwards (especially while St. Louis is out), Rangers coach Alain Vigneault reunited center Derek Stepan and wings Chris Kreider and Rick Nash. Stepan does not have a point in the past 10 games; Kreider has gone six games without a goal and Nash, who has 39 goals, has one goal in his past six.

Center Derick Brassard is expected to play with Kevin Hayes on the left and Mats Zuccarello on the right.

"I play with Rick on the penalty kill, and when I am out there with him, my job is to try to create space for him, for situations in which he can get a 1-on-1 situation or maybe challenge somebody and use his big body to get the puck to the net," Stepan said, according to the Daily News. "He shoots the puck too. If you look at his stats, I think he has 200 and some odd shots (260). He's a shooter.

"So it's important you understand that when he does have the puck to support him … and communicate with him. Because if he gives you the puck and you are able to give it back to him, he's going to be able to create space."</Article>
    <Category>IceHockey</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Rockets' Howard 'pretty close' to returning
By KRISTIE RIEKEN | Associated Press 
POSTED: Mar 18, 2015 5:35 PM ET
UPDATED: MAR 18, 2015 9:52 PM ET

AD
HOUSTON (AP) — Houston Rockets center Dwight Howard said Wednesday that his injured right knee is feeling better and he's close to returning to the court after a nearly two-month layoff.
Howard, who has missed the last 23 games due to swelling in the knee, returned to practice in the last week. He wouldn't give a timetable for his return, but his comments seemed to indicate it would be soon.
"I had a good eight weeks of really training and working on my body and mentally I feel good, physically I feel great so I can't wait to get back on the floor," he said.
Howard had a bone marrow aspirate injection in his knee on Feb. 9. Since then, he's gone through a grueling rehabilitation process that has included spending an inordinate amount of time on the treadmill.
"We did some extremely tough workouts on the treadmill. Anytime anyone says treadmill, I lose it," Howard joked. "I don't think anybody understands what they had me doing on the treadmill. I was just begging them: `Can I just play so I don't have to do this?' Rehab is harder than the actual practice and all of that stuff."
He said his knee no longer hurts, but that it's been a little achy in the past few days as he's started doing more full-contact work on the court.
"They've been doing a lot of different things to get me in shape, to get me moving and running," he said. "Each day they've been building up the test to see how far my body can go without breaking down or swelling in my knee or pain."
Howard has played just 32 games this season, averaging 16.3 points, 11 rebounds and 1.4 blocks a game.
It's the most games Howard has missed in his 11-year NBA career and it has been tough on him.
"My knee is something where I have to look out for the long run," the 29-year-old Howard said. "It's not just about this season but the rest of my career. As much as I would love to play through all the injuries, I just have to realize that the most important thing is my health."
The Rockets have gone 15-8 during this stretch without him and entered Wednesday's games in fourth place in the Western Conference.</Article>
    <Category>Basketball</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Former NBA player Jack Haley dead at 51
By Beth Harris | Associated Press 
POSTED: Mar 17, 2015 7:05 PM ET
UPDATED: MAR 17, 2015 10:28 PM ET

AD
LOS ANGELES (AP) — Jack Haley, who played nine seasons in the NBA including a reserve role on the Chicago Bulls' 1996 championship team, has died. He was 51.
Haley's family confirmed his death, saying the cause was heart disease. He died Monday at Los Alamitos Medical Center, according to the Orange County coroner's office website. There were no indications of foul play and an autopsy will be performed, the coroner said.
Haley played for the Bulls, New Jersey Nets, Los Angeles Lakers and San Antonio Spurs during his career, when he averaged 3.5 points and 2.7 rebounds mostly as a reserve. He sat out the entire 1992-93 season because of injury.
The Bulls drafted the 6-foot-10 forward-center as the 97th pick overall in 1987 out of UCLA, where he played three seasons and helped the Bruins with the NIT championship in 1985.
He graduated from Huntington Beach High and spent one season at Golden West College before transferring to UCLA. He played in Spain before joining the Bulls.
Haley had two different stints with the Bulls, starting his career with them and then returning to the team in 1995-96. He appeared in only the final game of the regular season, scoring five points in seven minutes. He didn't make the playoff roster, and the Michael Jordan-led Bulls set a record for victories in a season, going 72-10 on their way to winning the NBA title.
Haley was known on that team for his friendship with Bulls star Dennis Rodman, and he bristled at suggestions that he primarily served as a baby sitter for the eccentric rebounder.
"I've felt it's important to be a part of the greatest team in history and to get out and show people I'm not Dennis' babysitter," Haley told the Chicago Tribune. "I never have been. I've been a basketball player from Day One."
Rodman posted a photo of Haley kissing him on the cheek on Twitter, with the comment, "RIP to my brother Jack Haley. Sending love to his family."
Former Bulls star Scottie Pippen tweeted, "Very sorry to hear my old teammate, Jack Haley, has passed away. Great guy who I stayed in touch with over the years. RIP."
After his playing career ended, Haley worked as an assistant for the Nets under current Kentucky coach John Calipari, who tweeted, "Jack was one of the most positive, upbeat guys I've ever been around. He was on that unbelievable 1996 championship team in Chicago. Sad day."
Haley later worked as a broadcaster on Lakers telecasts. He lived in the Orange County city of Seal Beach.
"He cherished every moment and gave 100 percent whether on or off the court. And more than anything, Jack dearly loved his family. We are humbled and grateful for the outpouring of love, support, and prayers from around the country," Haley's family said in a statement issued Tuesday through the Lakers.
Lakers GM Mitch Kupchak said in a statement that Haley was "a hard worker and always very professional."
"He was proud to wear the Lakers uniform, and he was always a credit to our organization and the Lakers family," Kupchak said.
Haley appeared in the movies "Eddie" and "Rebound," and was in the music video for "Love in an Elevator" by Aerosmith.
He is survived by his sons Jack Jr. and Jeff, his mother Jeanette, brother Tim, sister Sondra and ex-wife Stacey.</Article>
    <Category>Basketball</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Goalie Darling delivers to power surging Blackhawks
Thursday, 03.19.2015 / 11:45 AM / Top Performer
NHL.com
CommentPrintE-mail
His Chicago Blackhawks facing the second of a back-to-back set against the top team in the NHL, coach Joel Quenneville decided to start rookie goalie Scott Darling over Corey Crawford against the New York Rangers on Wednesday at Madison Square Garden. Crawford is 6-0-1 with a 1.13 goals-against average and .964 save percentage in his past seven games but also made 38 saves Tuesday in a win against the New York Islanders at United Center.


Scott Darling

SCOTT DARLING
GOALIE - CHI
RECORD: 7-3-0
GAA: 1.96 | SVP: .936
Starting his first game in three weeks, Darling vindicated Quenneville's decision with 25 saves in a 1-0 win against the Rangers to give Chicago its fourth straight victory for the first time since winning eight straight in late November-early December.
Darling is 7-3-0 with a 1.96 GAA, .936 save percentage and his first NHL shutout.

"I'm just thrilled; it's an amazing stage to [get a shutout] at Madison Square Garden," Darling said. "It feels great to just get back in the net and do my job. This is one of the most famous arenas in the world against one of the most iconic jerseys there is. An 'Original Six' matchup on the NBC Sports Network; you really can't ask for much more."

Darling's finest moment came with 7:22 remaining in the first period. Rangers forward Rick Nash stole the puck from Blackhawks defenseman Brent Seabrook in Chicago's end of the ice and moved in alone on Darling. A couple of Nash dekes and a failed poke check put Darling on his back, but the 6-foot-6 Darling was able to stretch out and make the save with his left pad and keep the game scoreless.

Darling also made 10 saves in the third period to support forward Brad Richards' goal at 7:19 that gave the Blackhawks the victory.

"It was an impressive performance [by Darling]," Blackhawks defenseman Duncan Keith said. "He's a big goalie and there's not a lot to shoot at. He's aggressive and for a guy who hasn't played very much he was confident in his ability. That rubs off on everybody, so he was big part of the win."

The Blackhawks (43-21-6, 92 points) are 6-0-1 in the past seven games, two points behind the second-place Nashville Predators and three from the first-place St. Louis Blues in the Central Division.</Article>
    <Category>IceHockey</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>HALEP FIRST INTO FINAL FOUR
Carla Suárez Navarro was too tough in the first set, but Simona Halep took it to a whole new level in the next two sets to become the first player through to the semifinals.
Published March 18, 2015 12:14

Embed

INDIAN WELLS, CA, USA - Simona Halep took it to a whole new level after dropping the first set to make it past Carla Suárez Navarro and become the first player into the BNP Paribas Open semifinals.

Watch highlights, interviews and more video from Indian Wells right here on wtatennis.com!

Suárez Navarro could do no wrong in the opening stages of the match, winning the first four games in a row to go up 4-0, and even though Halep clawed her way back to 4-all, and then 5-all, Suárez Navarro regrouped just in time, closing out the 51-minute opening frame with a big forehand winner, 7-5.

That's where she was stopped in her tracks, though. The No.12-seeded Suárez Navarro watched on as the No.3-seeded Halep stormed through the next two sets in just 63 minutes to prevail, 5-7, 6-1, 6-1.

Halep finished the match off in style, blasting a big ace - her 28th winner of the match.

"She was opening the court pretty well with the angles, and it's really tough to play and hit the balls from wide in the court, so I knew I had to start playing more aggressively and hit more into the court," Halep explained in her on-court interview after the match. "I just tried to relax my body and my mind, fight for every point and play my best. And I'm happy to be in the semifinals here again.

"I'm looking forward to maybe playing the No.1 in the world again now!"

The World No.3 was referring to her potential semifinal opponent, Serena Williams, and it became a reality - the No.1-seeded Williams beat No.27 seed Timea Bacsinszky in the night-time quarterfinal.

Williams leads Halep in their head-to-head series, 4-1, but their two meetings at the BNP Paribas WTA Finals Singapore presented by SC Global last year are perhaps the most relevant - Halep beat Williams in the round robin, 6-0, 6-2, the equal-worst loss of Williams' career in terms of games won, but the American rebounded in a big way when they met again in the final a few days later, 6-3, 6-0.

"Serena is Serena. She's No.1 in the world. She's very strong," Halep said.

"It was a big day for me when I beat her. The biggest day, let's say. I learned that if I have the courage to go on court and just think I can win it, I can do it. If I'm nervous and I have emotions, it's much more difficult to play against her. You just have to believe and try your best, and try everything to win."</Article>
    <Category>Tennis</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Five things to consider after Dortmund 0-3 Juve
Published: Thursday 19 March 2015, 8.39CET
Juventus appear serious contenders for the European title after easing into the last eight at the expense of Borussia Dortmund, who, says Andy James, are in a period of transition.
by Andy James
from BVB Stadion Dortmund

EMAIL
PRINT
Five things to consider after Dortmund 0-3 Juve
Juventus players celebrate in front of their jubilant fans
©Getty Images

 
TRENDING NOW
1
Champions League quarter-final draw in depth
2
Champions League final tickets: Berlin 2015
3
UEFA.com's round of 16 team of the week
4
UEFA Champions League round of 16 by numbers
5
2015 final: Berlin
More
HEADLINES
Latest 
Team of the week
Round of 16 in numbers
Best of the second legs
Hunter on Barça-City
Download our podcast
More

 
The home crowd may have produced a spectacular choreographed display depicting Borussia Dortmund's 1997 UEFA Champions League final triumph against Juventus prior to kick-off, but the hosts' performance in Wednesday's round of 16 re-run could hardly have been further removed from the Schwarzgelben's night of glory in Munich 18 years ago.

RELATED ITEMS
Tévez leads Juve through
Allegri eyes 'magical four'
'A special night for us'
Barcelona knock out City
Download our podcast
Down but not out
Date for last-eight draws
Lichtsteiner's Juve joy
Indeed, the pre-match mosaic in the stands sparkled considerably more than Dortmund's showing on the pitch as Massimiliano Allegri's visitors expertly dispatched their opponents to cruise into the quarter finals by way of a 3-0 victory that took them through 5-1 on aggregate.

UEFA.com picks out five points to consider from a thoroughly positive evening for the Bianconeri.

Juventus are serious contenders
Looking at the Juventus starting lineup before the game, it was clear just how much quality they possess – even without the injured Andrea Pirlo. Another big name, Paul Pogba, was forced to withdraw early on, but even with two key midfielders missing, the likes of Arturo Vidal and Claudio Marchisio put in top-class performances to ensure it was the Italians who were always in control. Their defence was resolute throughout, two-goal Carlos Tévez outstanding in attack. Put simply, it was difficult to identify any obvious weaknesses in this burgeoning Juventus team and they have every reason to believe they can go far in this competition.


Lichtsteiner: Tévez's early goal was key
Dortmund beaten at their own game
Tévez's early stunner certainly changed the complexion of the match, but from there Juventus were tactically immaculate. Dortmund boss Jürgen Klopp had said before the game that it would be difficult to play against an Italian side who only needed a draw and, once the Serie A leaders were in front, it was twice the task. Juve defended superbly in the first half, suffocating the space between the lines and forcing Dortmund to abandon their quick-passing game for uncharacteristic long balls. In the second period the visitors showed similar intelligence, soaking up pressure and counterattacking to kill off the tie in the kind of lethal manner previous BVB teams would have been proud of.

Reus riled by Vidal
Any hopes of Dortmund reversing the 2-1 first-leg deficit relied heavily on Marco Reus. Juventus, and particularly former Bayer 04 Leverkusen midfielder Vidal, knew this and set about shutting him out of the game early on. Vidal, well-acquainted with Reus from his time in the Bundesliga, put in two or three hefty challenges in the opening period. Some arguably challenged the rules, but if intimidation was the aim of the game, it worked. Reus, riled by the rough treatment he was receiving, reacted petulantly at one stage with a little shove off the ball. His touch was also surprisingly sloppy at times, especially in the first half, and ultimately the normally explosive winger was unable to muster a shot on target.

BVB's bubble has burst
As the Juventus fans celebrated with their heroes, the Dortmund support saluted their troops in a manner which, while on the one hand was admirable, belied a general sense of resignation that this BVB squad's heyday has passed. The performance was their most unthreatening at this level in recent memory and a 14th defeat in all competitions this term leaves the club facing the prospect of a season without European football for the first time since 2009/10.


The 1997 final: Dortmund v Juventus
Stars such as Robert Lewandowski and Mario Götze are long gone and it was that kind of extra class which inspired Dortmund to two Bundesliga titles and the 2013 UEFA Champions League final. The current team, though talented, do not boast quite the same pedigree – Kevin Kampl and Adrián Ramos are only getting their first taste of Europe's premier club competition this season – and the fans appear to accept that the time has come for Dortmund to regroup and plot their next long-term assault on the continent's elite.

Power shift in the offing?
The Bundesliga has enjoyed a boom period this decade, with FC Bayern München reaching three of the last five UEFA Champions League finals and Dortmund joining them in 2013. Germany has overtaken Italy in the UEFA five-year coefficients in that timeframe, with the majority of their European representatives making it to the knockout stage throughout. This season things have transpired somewhat differently, Bayern notwithstanding. Just two of Germany's seven clubs (Bayern and VfL Wolfsburg) remain in European competition at the time of writing, while Italy still have all six of their teams gunning for glory. They will be hoping to close the gap in the rankings with continued success in this season’s tournaments. Juventus, no doubt, will be spearheading that particular offensive.</Article>
    <Category>Football</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Tunis Bardo museum: Nine suspects arrested for links to attack
Tunisian security forces stand guard outside the National Bardo Museum in Tunis. 19 March 2015
Security is being heightened following the attack on the museum in Tunis
Continue reading the main story
Related Stories

Survivors' stories
Tunisia militants: How big a threat?
Media galvanized by Tunis attack
Nine people have been arrested in connection with a gun attack in Tunis that saw 23 people killed on Wednesday, including 20 foreign tourists.

Tunisia's presidency said four of those arrested were directly linked to the attack and five had "ties to the cell".

The army will also be deployed to major cities, the presidency added.

In another development, Islamic State said it was behind the attack on the Bardo museum, using an audio message to praise two "knights of the caliphate".

The message, posted on Twitter accounts known to be reliable sources of IS propaganda, named the attackers as Abu-Zakariya al-Tunisi and Abu-Anas al-Tunisi.

A statement described the attack as a "blessed invasion of one of the dens of infidels and vice in Muslim Tunisia".

Jump media playerMedia player helpOut of media player. Press enter to return or tab to continue.
James Reynolds says the day of the attack on Tunisia's most famous museum has become known as 'Black Wednesday'
One of two gunmen involved in the Bardo museum attack, named by Tunisian officials as Yassine Laabidi, was reportedly known to the authorities.

Tunisian Prime Minister Habib Essid told RTL Radio that security services had flagged him up but were not aware of "anything specific", or of any links to known militant groups.

Laabidi and his accomplice, named as Hatem Khachnaoui, were killed as security forces stormed the museum.

It was not immediately clear how the identities of the gunmen corresponded to the names given by IS. Jihadist groups, including IS, often give their fighters noms de guerre.

Tourists from Japan, Colombia, Australia, the UK, and several other European countries were killed in the attack and more than 40 people were injured.

line
Analysis by Frank Gardner, BBC security correspondent
The claim by so-called Islamic State, if authentic, that it carried out Wednesday's attack in Tunis, needs to be seen in context. IS does not control any territory in Tunisia, there is no IS "province" as exists in Syria and Iraq.

Tunisia, unlike its unfortunate neighbour Libya, is a modern, functioning state with an elected government and trained police and security forces. That said, Tunisia suffers from a number of factors that make it ripe for exploitation by IS, which would surely like to include it in an eventual string of North African provinces stretching all the way from Egypt to Nigeria.

Between 3,000 and 5,000 Tunisians have gone to join IS, with an estimated 500 having returned. There is chaos to the east in Libya and jihadists hiding on the border with Algeria. There are also many young, dissatisfied Tunisians who feel economically and politically frustrated, the very reason why Tunisia became the birthplace of the Arab Spring in 2011.

Islamic State builds on al-Qaeda lands

line
The suspects arrested on Thursday were not identified and no further details were given of their alleged involvement.

However, BBC security correspondent Frank Gardner says an al-Qaeda operative has claimed that the two gunmen had spent two months training with militants in Derna, eastern Libya, before slipping back into Tunisia.

In a statement, Tunisia's presidency said the country was facing "exceptional circumstances".

"After a meeting with the armed forces, the president has decided large cities will be secured by the army," the statement added.

Tourism hit
As Tunisia attempted to come to terms with the attack, a large anti-terrorism protest was allowed through the museum's gates to the site of the attack on Thursday afternoon.

People carried banners calling for peace and lit candles in memory of the dead.

Anti-terrorism demonstration at the Bardo museum. 19 March 2015
A large anti-terror protest took place at the Bardo museum on Thursday
Witnesses to the attack said the gunmen, carrying assault rifles, opened fire on tourists outside the museum in front of a row of buses before charging inside and taking hostages.

On Thursday, two Spanish tourists and a Tunisian museum worker were found at the museum after having hidden there overnight believing the attack might not have been over, police said.

Tunisia tourist datapic
The attack is a huge blow for Tunisia's tourism industry and its government, which only emerged at the end of a long political transition several months ago, the BBC's Arab affairs editor Sebastian Usher says.

Two cruise companies - MSC Cruises and Costa Cruises - said they were suspending stopovers in Tunis.

MSC said in a statement that at least nine of those killed had been passengers on its MSC Splendida cruise ship which was docked in Tunis. It said another 12 of its passengers were injured and six were still unaccounted for.

Costa said that three passengers from the Costa Fascinosa had died. Eight others were injured and two were unaccounted for, company CEO Michael Thamm said.

line
Who were the victims?
According to Tunisian authorities, 23 people were killed - though it is not clear if totals provided by the authorities include the gunmen. Some of the countries involved have given different totals and not all the dead have been identified. The dead include:

At least three Tunisians, including a police officer involved in the security operation
Five Japanese were killed, according to Mr Essid - although Japan says it has only confirmed the deaths of three citizens
Four Italians
Two Colombians
Two Spaniards
One national each from the UK, Australia, France and Poland
Survivors' stories

line
Blood stains on the ground near the entrance to the museum. 19 March 2015
The area outside the museum is still covered in blood stains from the attack
At the time of the attack, deputies in the neighbouring parliament building were discussing anti-terrorism legislation.

Sayida Ounissi, an MP, told BBC Radio Four's Today programme that according to the security services the gunmen had originally planned to attack parliament.

A statement released by a jihadist media outlet gave a similar account, saying the gunmen began killing tourists after being repelled by police at the parliament. The statement did not say which group carried out the attack.

Tunisia began a transition to democracy in 2011 with the overthrow of long-serving ruler Zine al-Abidine Ben Ali.

Hardline Islamists have tried hard to derail the process and security concerns have increased as neighbouring Libya has become increasingly unstable.

A large number of Tunisians have also left to fight in Syria and Iraq, triggering worries that returning militants could carry out attacks at home.

Tunisia's Culture Minister, Latifa Lakhdar, told reporters that the museum would re-open to the public early next week.</Article>
    <Category>NoSport</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Wenger on Arsenal, Henry and a Monaco reunion
Published: Sunday 22 February 2015, 11.00CET
As Arsène Wenger prepares for a meeting between two clubs that have been his life for 25 years, he discusses his time at AS Monaco FC, Thierry Henry and Arsenal FC's quarter-final aim.
by Simon Hart
from London

EMAIL
PRINT
Wenger on Arsenal, Henry and a Monaco reunion
Arsène Wenger is in his 19th season at Arsenal
©AFP/Getty Images

 
TRENDING NOW
1
Champions League quarter-final draw in depth
2
Champions League final tickets: Berlin 2015
3
UEFA.com's round of 16 team of the week
4
2015 final: Berlin
5
UEFA Champions League round of 16 by numbers
More
HEADLINES
Latest 
Team of the week
Round of 16 in numbers
Best of the second legs
Hunter on Barça-City
Download our podcast
More

 
UEFA.com: How did you feel when Monaco were pulled out of the hat at the draw?

RELATED ITEMS
#AskSilva
Arsenal-Monaco links
Control key for Moutinho
Arsenal v Monaco facts
Arsenal v Monaco preview
Arsène Wenger: To be honest it was a surprise, because I always expect the most prestigious team to come out against us – that has happened the last five or six years. It's also one of those strange coincidences in life, because between them these two clubs account for 25 years of my life. That's very unusual, to meet in the Champions League. It was a little bit of an emotional shock.

UEFA.com: You finished second in your group again. After the previous four seasons and the setbacks you have had at this stage, was that a concern?

Wenger: It was, yes! We were always in difficult groups, and this year we were level on points with Dortmund but finished second in the group. It was a big concern, because we [previously] got Bayern, Barcelona, AC Milan, with the second game obviously away. But this time I think it's 50-50 and that means we have a chance. It will be down to the quality of our performance.

UEFA.com: We all know about Arsenal's attacking qualities, while Monaco conceded only once in the group stage; how do you see the first leg in north London?

Wenger: When the first game is at home, you play with the desire to score but know that every goal you concede can be deadly. You must find a balance between free-spirited attacking and being cautious enough to defend well – that will be down to experience. We have experience in this competition; this is a good opportunity to show it.

©Bob Thomas/Getty Images
After reaching the Cup Winners' Cup final
UEFA.com: At Monaco you promoted young players and had them playing attractive football, and at Arsenal you have done the same. Are you proud to have made that mark on both clubs?

Wenger: Yes, I am very proud of having achieved that because I have the good fortune to be in a job where I can influence people's lives in a positive way. What's strange for me is that the guys I helped at the start of their careers, like [Lilian] Thuram, [Emmanuel] Petit, have already finished their careers. You are always happy when they have fantastic careers; helping players achieve something in life provides a very positive feeling.

UEFA.com: Looking back to some of your adventures with Monaco, what do you feel when you recall the 1992 European Cup Winners' Cup final against Werder Bremen?

Wenger: Sadness. The night before, in France, we had a huge disaster in Bastia [18 died when a stand collapsed ahead of a French Cup semi-final], and we couldn't go to bed after that, and we couldn't prepare properly for the game. It was a bit similar to the [2006] Champions League final, because we didn't lose a game all season, just the final.

But when I arrived in Monaco, the club had never gone further than the first round, so the fact that we played a Cup Winners' Cup final, the fact we played in a Champions League semi-final, that we went far in UEFA Cups, was an achievement. They reached the Champions League final, too, after I left.

UEFA.com: Regarding that run to the 1994 UEFA Champions League semi-finals with such a talented team and some big names, how much did you enjoy that time and what lessons did you learn?

Wenger: It was very important for me. We were in a group with Barcelona; we played AC Milan, the big team at the time. It was a very interesting experience. Since then, of course, I have had over 180 games in the Champions League, but you never get used to playing in the Champions League because it's always a privilege to play against the best teams in Europe.

©AFP/Getty Images
With Thierry Henry after the 2006 final
UEFA.com: One man associated with both Arsenal and Monaco is Thierry Henry. What made him stand out when he was a teenager in France?

Wenger: He had exceptional technical qualities, a good understanding of the game and was a super athlete too. And his pace, his power, was frightening: he had it all. He was 17 when I gave him his first start and I could see something special. He was a world champion at 19 and enjoyed such a huge career, even if he had a difficult period when he went to Italy. He came here [to Arsenal] at the age of 21 and he quickly became the superstar he deserved to be.</Article>
    <Category>Football</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Five talking points from Arsenal v Monaco
Published: Thursday 26 February 2015, 1.24CET
AS Monaco FC's discipline and control were in sharp contrast to the way Arsenal FC were picked apart as the French side's 3-1 win put them in charge of the last-16 tie.
by Michael Harrold
from Arsenal Stadium

EMAIL
PRINT
Five talking points from Arsenal v Monaco
Alexis Sánchez stands dejected as Monaco celebrate
©Getty Images

 
TRENDING NOW
1
Champions League quarter-final draw in depth
2
Champions League final tickets: Berlin 2015
3
UEFA.com's round of 16 team of the week
4
2015 final: Berlin
5
UEFA Champions League round of 16 by numbers
More
HEADLINES
Latest 
Team of the week
Round of 16 in numbers
Best of the second legs
Hunter on Barça-City
Download our podcast
More

 
1 Fabinho rose to the challenge
Winning at Arsenal FC is an achievement at any time in the UEFA Champions League; for AS Monaco FC to do so with a raft of injuries and without suspended captain Jérémy Toulalan was exceptional. The noise of their celebrations in the dressing room afterwards said how much this meant to them, and their performance was epitomised by UEFA man of the match Fabinho, who had switched from right-back to central midfield to deputise for Toulalan.

RELATED ITEMS
Schmidt's Bayer delight
Monaco's princely plan
Leverkusen secure lead
Wenger on Arsenal-Monaco
Juve v Dortmund conclusions
Riling Suárez cost City
Kompany bemoans first half
Monaco catch Arsenal cold
In contrast to Arsenal, Fabinho was able to hold the space in front of the back four and constantly disrupt his opponents' moves. Fabinho was quick to point out, though, that there is plenty of work still to do. "We celebrated a lot but we know there is another match to come, another 90 minutes – so we have to continue as Arsenal are a big team. It will be a difficult match." 

2 Déjà vu for Arsenal
There was a sense of déjà vu about Arsenal's collapse. Against RSC Anderlecht on matchday four the Gunners had surrendered a 3-0 lead in the second half. They did not have the advantage this time and the goals conceded could have a far greater impact. In both games the opposition exploited with ease the gaps when Arsenal attacks broke down, and here Dimitar Berbatov and Yannick Ferreira-Carrasco were the beneficiaries with the second and third goals.

Arsenal's form has picked up since the introduction of Francis Coquelin in the holding role – so much so that this was just their third defeat in 14 matches – but this looked like a return to the defensively fragile side from the start of the campaign.


Fabinho delight at Monaco away goals
3 Berbatov thrives on return
By comparison, Monaco were a model of discipline and control, confident and tidy in possession, keeping their passes simple and playing with impressive calm as exemplified by Berbatov and João Moutinho – who were both happy to hold the ball and wait for their chances. Berbatov's strike was crucial, the 34-year-old former Tottenham Hotspur FC forward returning to the home of his old rivals to rub salt into wounds.

4 Gunners need target practice
Arsenal enjoyed more possession (55% to 45%), and carved out more opportunities (14 to Monaco's 10), yet ultimately they were beaten by the more clinical team. Of Monaco's ten shots at goal, seven were on target and three went in – whereas Arsenal mustered just four shots on target from 14 attempts.

Olivier Giroud drew the greatest groan from the crowd when he skied over after Danijel Subašić had parried Alexis Sánchez's effort into his path. Monaco also rode their luck, Geoffrey Kondogbia scoring via a deflection from Per Mertesacker and Danny Welbeck blocking Theo Walcott's goalbound drive – but they earned it.


Welbeck: First goal was crucial
5 What next?
For the third season in a row, Arsenal have lost the first leg at home in the round of 16. If Alex Oxlade-Chamberlain's late goal appeared to have given the Gunners a lifeline, Ferreira-Carrasco's swift reply cancelled that out.

Arsenal still have the firepower to cause Monaco problems at the Stade Louis II, yet it is hard to see Leonardo Jardim's side – who have shipped only two goals in seven games so far in the competition – letting in three in one. "We had the chances but we didn't take them and we were suicidal defensively," Arsène Wenger said. "It is very, very disappointing."</Article>
    <Category>Football</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Champions League round of 16 draw
Published: Monday 15 December 2014, 12.33CET
There will be rapid reunions for FC Barcelona and Manchester City FC, Real Madrid CF and FC Schalke 04, and Chelsea FC and Paris Saint-Germain after the draw in Nyon.
PRINT

E-MAIL
PRINT
arrowarrow
Atlético start the knockout phase with a trip to Leverkusen
©Getty Images for UEFA
3/16
counter
Previous
Chelsea are chosen to play Paris during the UEFA Champions League round of 16 draw at the House of European Football in NyonManchester City are handed a stellar tie against BarcelonaAtlético start the knockout phase with a trip to LeverkusenJuventus and Dortmund will face off in a repeat of the 1997 finalHolders Real Madrid will face Schalke again this seasonBayern make the trip to Shakhtar for their round of 16 first legThe draw is completed as Porto are picked to meet BaselKarl-Heinz Riedle helps make the UEFA Champions League round of 16 drawEmilio Butragueño looks on ahead of the eventGiorgio Marchetti, UEFA competitions director, outlines the draw processUEFA General Secretary Gianni Infantino welcomes attendees to NyonPavel Nedvěd awaits the drawThe trophy is polished ahead of the proceedingsThe draw pots on stage for the selectionThe draw balls are and pots are prepared backstageA close-up view of the Real Madrid ball
Next

 
TRENDING NOW
1
Champions League quarter-final draw in depth
2
Champions League final tickets: Berlin 2015
3
UEFA.com's round of 16 team of the week
4
2015 final: Berlin
5
UEFA Champions League round of 16 by numbers
More
HEADLINES
Latest 
Team of the week
Round of 16 in numbers
Best of the second legs
Hunter on Barça-City
Download our podcast
More

 
There will be a number of reunions in the UEFA Champions League round of 16 following the draw in Nyon, with three of the ties having been played in last season's competition.

RELATED ITEMS
Round of 16 classics
Best of matchday six
Group stage records
Download our podcast
Round of 32 draw
Route to Nyon mapped
FC Barcelona and Real Madrid CF saw off Manchester City FC and FC Schalke 04 respectively at this stage in 2013/14 and will hope for a repeat performance this time round. Chelsea FC beat Paris Saint-Germain in the quarter-finals and are paired with the French side again, while there are historically significant ties between Juventus and Borussia Dortmund, and Arsenal FC and AS Monaco FC – in the latter case due to the Arsène Wenger connection.

Round of 16 draw:
17 February &amp; 11 March
Paris Saint-Germain (FRA) v Chelsea FC (ENG)
FC Shakhtar Donetsk (UKR) v FC Bayern München (GER)
18 February &amp; 10 March
FC Schalke 04 (GER) v Real Madrid CF (ESP)
FC Basel 1893 (SUI) v FC Porto (POR)
24 February &amp; 18 March
Manchester City FC (ENG) v FC Barcelona (ESP)
Juventus (ITA) v Borussia Dortmund (GER)
25 February &amp; 17 March
Bayer 04 Leverkusen (GER) v Club Atlético de Madrid (ESP)
Arsenal FC (ENG) v AS Monaco FC (FRA)

• FULL SCHEDULE

Road to Berlin
Quarter-final draw: 20 March
Quarter-finals: 14/15 &amp; 21/22 April
Semi-final draw: 24 April
Semi-finals: 5/6 &amp; 12/13 May
Final (Olympiastadion, Berlin): 20.45CET, 6 June

Draw facts
• Dortmund overcame Juventus 3-1 in the 1997 UEFA Champions League final in Munich; the Italian team had won 6-1 over two legs in the UEFA Cup final four years earlier.

• Paris took on Chelsea in last season's quarter-finals, the Londoners retrieving a 3-1 first-leg defeat with a 2-0 victory at Stamford Bridge to progress on away goals.

• Manchester City-Barcelona is another repeat of a 2013/14 encounter, the Spanish club prevailing 2-0 in Manchester and 2-1 at home in last season's round of 16.

• Real Madrid overwhelmed Schalke in the round of 16 last term, winning 6-1 in Gelsenkirchen and 3-1 in Spain; Cristiano Ronaldo scored four times in the tie.

• Atlético and Leverkusen played out two 1-1 draws in the 2010/11 UEFA Europa League group stage.

• Shakhtar and Bayern, and Porto and Basel have never met before.

• While Arsenal and Monaco have never played each other before, Arsène Wenger was in charge of Monaco between 1987 and 1994, winning Ligue 1 (1988) and the Coupe de France (1991). Monaco also reached the 1992 European Cup Winners' Cup final under Wenger, losing 2-0 to SV Werder Bremen.</Article>
    <Category>Football</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Yemen crisis: Air raid on president's palace in Aden
Forces loyal to Yemen's President  Abdrabbuh Mansour Hadi guard his compound in Aden (25 February 2015)
Aden has been President Hadi's base since he fled the capital Sanaa last month
Continue reading the main story
Yemen unrest

Power struggle
Heightened anxiety
Who are the Houthis?
Security nightmare
Warplanes have targeted the palace used by Yemen's President Abdrabbuh Mansour Hadi in the southern city of Aden.

Officials said anti-aircraft guns prevented any direct hits on the hilltop compound. But witnesses saw smoke rising from the area afterwards.

It is not clear if Mr Hadi was inside, but aides said he was now safe.

Earlier, there were clashes at Aden's airport between troops and militiamen loyal to Mr Hadi and those backing his predecessor and the Houthi rebels.

At least six people were killed as the president's forces repelled an assault, which forced the airport's temporary closure.

Aden has been the president's base since he fled the Sanaa last month, after being placed under effective house arrest by the rebels when they took full control of the capital in January and declared that a five-member "presidential council" would rule the country.

'Under control'
The deputy editor of the al-Ayam newspaper in Aden, Bashraheel Bashraheel, told the BBC that he heard fighter jets flying over the city at about 15:30 local time (12:30 GMT).

"Then we heard a loud bang and anti-aircraft guns firing from the presidential palace," he added. "Some witnesses who live within a few hundred metres of the palace saw smoke coming out of the buildings."

Militiamen loyal to President Abdrabbuh Mansour Hadi after fighting in Aden (19 March 2015)
At least five people were killed in Thursday's clashes at Aden's international airport
A man stranded at the Aden International Airport, waits as heavy gun battles between a unit of police commandos loyal to President Ali Abdullah Saleh and security forces loyal to the current president intensified in Aden
Passengers were stranded at the terminal during the fighting, but flights later resumed
Officials said the warplanes fired at the compound but missed the palace, hitting a nearby hillside. No damaged was caused and no-one was believed to have been hurt, they added.

A security source told the Reuters news agency that the situation "was under control and there was nothing to be worried about".

It was not immediately clear if the president was inside the palace at the time of the attack.

One of Mr Hadi's aides told the Associated Press that he had not been there, but another was quoted by the AFP news agency as saying that the president had now been "evacuated to a safe place".

The officials said the planes were flown by pilots allied to the Houthis and former President Ali Abdullah Saleh, who handed over power to Mr Hadi in 2011 after mass protests against his rule.

Sky News Arabia reported that the planes had taken off from al-Dulaimi air base in Sanaa.

Map showing Houthi areas of influence
The fighting at Aden's airport began when troops from the Special Security Forces, a police unit loyal to Mr Saleh, stormed the facility after claiming that they had been fired on from nearby buildings, an army official told the New York Times.

Mr Hadi's forces regained control of the airport after reinforcements arrived with tanks and armoured vehicles several hours later.

The army official said they were now moving to take control of the Special Security Forces' headquarters.

The president tried earlier this month to dismiss the head of the unit, Gen Abdul Hafez al-Saqqaf, in a bid to strengthen his hold on Aden.

Correspondents say the air raid on the compound and the fighting at the airport suggest the Houthis and Mr Saleh's supporters are taking the battle to President Hadi in Aden in order to prevent him from consolidating his new power base in the south.</Article>
    <Category>NoSport</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Virginia governor calls for inquiry into student arrest
Martese Johnson, 20, was arrested outside a Charlottesville's pub on 18 March.
Martese Johnson, 20, was arrested outside a Charlottesville's pub on Wednesday
Continue reading the main story
Related Stories

Is the US justice system racist? Watch
How one shooting sparked national protests
The governor of Virginia has called for an investigation into the violent arrest of a black US student.

Alcoholic Beverage Control (ABC) agents arrested Martese Johnson, 20, outside a Charlottesville's pub early on Wednesday, sparking protests at the University of Virginia.

A video and photos of Mr Johnson covered in blood and being pushed to the ground were widely circulated.

The white agents said Mr Johnson "was very agitated and belligerent".

But Bryan Beaubrun, a University of Virginia (UVA) student who photographed the arrest, said police acted with unnecessary force.

"He didn't need to be tackled. He wasn't being aggressive at all," Mr Beaubrun told the Associated Press.

In a statement, ABC says that "uniformed ABC Agents observed and approached" an unidentified individual "after he was refused entry to a licensed establishment" just after midnight on Wednesday in an area of bars and restaurants near the university campus known as "the Corner."

According to court records Mr Johnson was charged with obstruction of justice without force, and public swearing or intoxication.

"Governor McAuliffe is concerned by the reports of this incident and has asked the secretary of public safety to initiate an independent Virginia State Police investigation into the use of force," the Democratic governor's office said.

University of Virginia student Martese Johnson was arrested in Charlottesville on Wednesday
Martese Johnson is a third year student at the University of Virginia
The state's Department of Alcoholic Beverage Control said it would cooperate with the investigation.

The agents involved have been placed on administrative duties. ABC agents focus on alcohol-related violations but are considered state-wide police officers with authority to arrest.

On Wednesday evening, hundreds of students held a protest on the UVA campus to demand justice for Mr Johnson.

Flanked by fellow students, Mr Johnson - with his face bruised and covered in stitches - was on hand for the event,

"I beg for you guys to please respect everyone here," Mr Johnson told the crowd. "We really are one community."

Mr Johnson's lawyer, Daniel P Watkins, said his client is a third-year UVA student, studying Italian and Media Studies.</Article>
    <Category>NoSport</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>IS Yazidi attacks may be genocide, says UN
Displaced people from the minority Yazidi sect, fleeing violence from forces loyal to the Islamic State in Sinjar town - August 11, 2014
Yazidis came under attack in the Sinjar area of Iraq last summer
Continue reading the main story
Islamic State

Pushing back
Who is Mohammed Emwazi?
Subject people?
IS uses videos to shock
Jihadists from the Islamic State (IS) group may have committed genocide and war crimes against the minority Yazidi community in Iraq, the UN says.

In a new report, it says IS had "the intent... to destroy the Yazidi as a group."

Tens of thousands of Yazidis fled villages in northern Iraq amid IS advances last summer. Many were killed, captured and enslaved.

Yazidis follow an ancient faith that jihadists regard as devil worship.

The report, commissioned by the UN Office of the High Commissioner for Human Rights, was based on more than 100 interviews with survivors of attacks in Iraq between June 2014 and February this year.

Among the atrocities it says were perpetrated against the Yazidi community by IS (also known as ISIL), were:

the "brutal and targeted" killing of hundreds of men and boys in Nineveh province, northwest of Baghdad, in August 2014;
the rape of girls as young as six;
the abduction of women "as spoils of war";
the forced separation of families, with boys as young as eight taken to be trained as IS fighters.
The reports adds: "In some instances, villages were entirely emptied of their Yazidi population."

A statement by the UNHCR says: "One witness described how two ISIL members sat laughing as two teenage girls were raped in the next room.

"A pregnant woman, repeatedly raped by an ISIL 'doctor' over a period of two and a half months, said he deliberately sat on her stomach.

"He told her: 'This baby should die because it is an infidel; I can make a Muslim baby'. "

Displaced Iraqi families from the Yazidi community cross the Iraqi-Syrian border at the Fishkhabur crossing, in northern Iraq, on August 13, 2014.
A new UN-backed report says Islamic State probably tried 'to destroy the Yazidi as a group'.
The plight of the Yazidi population was brought to international attention when IS captured the town of Sinjar in August 2014.

Thousands of residents, mainly Yazidis, were forced to flee.

Many were trapped on nearby Mount Sinjar, which was surrounded by IS fighters.

Airstrikes led by the Unites States, and an offensive led by Kurdish peshmerga forces, helped break the stranglehold on Mount Sinjar.

Grey line
Who are the Yazidis?
Jump media playerMedia player helpOut of media player. Press enter to return or tab to continue.
Yazidis revere the Bible and Koran - but much of their tradition is oral
Religious sect found in northern Iraq, Syria and the Caucasus
Religion incorporates elements of many faiths, including Zoroastrianism
Principal divine figure, Malak Taus (Peacock Angel), is the supreme angel of the seven angels who ruled the universe after it was created by God
Many Muslims and other groups incorrectly view Yazidis as devil worshippers
There are estimated to be around 500,000 Yazidis worldwide, most living in Iraq's Nineveh plains
In August 2007 jihadists attacked Yazidi villages in Nineveh, killing between 400 and 700 people
Who, What, Why: Who are the Yazidis?

Iraq: The minorities of Nineveh

Grey line
As well as looking into offences against the Yazidi community, investigators reported on crimes against other ethnic groups.

The report says 600 male prisoners - mainly Shia Muslims - were driven to a ravine in June 2014 and shot. It says some survived because bodies fell on top of them. Islamic State considers Shia Muslims as heretics.

On 12 June 2014, the report adds, between 1,500 and 1,700 cadets from the Speicher army base, near Tikrit, were killed after surrendering to IS fighters.

Iraqi government reports into both massacres have not yet been made public.

An image grab taken from a propaganda video uploaded on June 11 2014 by jihadist group the Islamic State
IS militants killed up to 1,700 cadets in a massacre in June 2014, the reports says
'Extrajudicial killings'
The report also warns of offences being committed by Iraqi security forces and affiliated militia.

It says they "carried out extrajudicial killings, torture, abductions and forcibly displaced a large number of people, often with impunity." It adds that they "may have committed war crimes".

Iraq's government has not yet responded to the report.

Iraq is not currently a member of the International Criminal Court in The Hague. If any crimes there were to be investigated by the ICC, Iraq would have to become a member.

Any offences defined as international crimes by the ICC would also have to be criminalised under Iraq's domestic laws.

The report urges Iraq to join the ICC, and also calls on the UN Security Council to refer the case to The Hague.</Article>
    <Category>NoSport</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>SERENA &amp; HALEP TO CLASH IN SFS
Serena Williams ended Timea Bacsinszky's 15-match winning streak to extend her own winning streak to 15 and reach the BNP Paribas Open semis. Simona Halep awaits.
Published March 18, 2015 12:15

Embed

INDIAN WELLS, CA, USA - Serena Williams ended the 15-match winning streak of Timea Bacsinszky on Wednesday night to reach the BNP Paribas Open semifinals, where she'll face Simona Halep.

Watch highlights, interviews and more video from Indian Wells right here on wtatennis.com!

The No.27-seeded Bacsinszky had been in the zone for weeks - that 15-match winning streak included back-to-back WTA titles in Acapulco and Monterrey and three more wins here. It looked like she might threaten Williams, as well, as she broke in the first game of the match and rode that to a 3-1 lead.

But the No.1-seeded Williams had her own winning streak going, 14 in a row coming into this match, and she battled back to keep it alive, beating Bacsinszky for her own 15th win in a row, 7-5, 6-3.

"I played well, but sometimes playing well isn't enough against Serena," Bacsinszky said. "I think I was giving her a hard time, so I give all the credit to her - she was just stronger out there today."

Bacsinszky was more solid in the match, committing 22 unforced errors to Williams' 31, but Williams was just too aggressive - she had more than twice as many winners as Bacsinszky, 23 to 11.

"She was on a winning streak, so I was like, 'I hope I win tonight, because she hasn't lost in a really long time!'" Williams said on court. "But she has a great future. She's already making a future now."

The World No.1 then addressed her adoring fans in the crowd. "I'm just happy to still be here playing in front of you guys. It's completely unexpected. I can't believe I'm still here and still at the event."

Up next for Williams is the No.3-seeded Halep, who dropped the first set but then ran away with it in the next two sets to beat No.12-seeded Carla Suárez Navarro earlier in the day, 5-7, 6-1, 6-1.

Williams leads Halep in their head-to-head series, 4-1, but that one loss was painful - in the round robin portion of the BNP Paribas WTA Finals Singapore presented by SC Global last year, Williams lost to Halep, 6-0, 6-2, which was the equal-worst loss of her entire career in terms of games won. It was also the first time in the history of the WTA where a Romanian beat the reigning No.1 player in the world.

She rebounded very well when they played a few days later in the final though, winning, 6-3, 6-0.

"Those matches were totally different," Williams said. "What I take out most is to be ready. I expect her to be playing an incredible game. I don't think I was necessarily ready for that the first time.

"I'm ready for her to be the great player that she's capable of being."</Article>
    <Category>Tennis</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>8 PLAYERS, 41 GRAND SLAMS
There's some tennis royalty in the doubles semifinals of the BNP Paribas Open - the eight players left have won a combined total of 41 Grand Slams. Who has the most?
Published March 18, 2015 12:13

8 Players, 41 Grand Slams Lisa Raymond, Samantha Stosur
INDIAN WELLS, CA, USA - An all-star doubles semifinal line-up has been brewing at the BNP Paribas Open over the last few days, with the eight players left holding 41 Grand Slam titles between them.

The first team to move through to the final four was the No.1-seeded pairing of Martina Hingis and Sania Mirza, who continued to cruise in their first ever tournament together, rallying from an early 3-0 hole to beat the wildcard pairing of Daniela Hantuchova and Karin Knapp on Tuesday, 6-4, 6-2.

Later on Tuesday, Lisa Raymond and Sam Stosur - unseeded now, but the No.1 team in the world in years past - cruised past Shahar Peer and Vera Zvonareva, 6-2, 6-1, to book their semifinal spot.

"I think we both played really well," Stosur said. "It's like each match we're starting to find a really good rhythm and play really well together. It's nice to be out there with Lisa again.

"We're trying to have a good run, so yeah, it's good fun!"

"I think it was a solid performace from Sam and I," Raymond said. "It's been a fun week getting back on the court with Sam. We've had so much success together and we're such good friends, and we both love playing out here at Indian Wells. We're just really psyched to be back in the semifinals."

Raymond and Stosur have two Grand Slam doubles titles together - the 2005 US Open and 2006 French Open - and they spent 39 weeks as co-World No.1s together in 2006 and 2007.

The other two quarterfinals took place on Wednesday, with Klaudia Jans-Ignacik and Andreja Klepac defeating Sabine Lisicki and Andrea Petkovic, 7-6(5), 7-6(7), and No.2 seeds Ekaterina Makarova and Elena Vesnina getting the better of No.7 seeds Caroline Garcia and Katarina Srebotnik, 7-5, 6-4.

"We lost to them the last time we played them in Dubai, so we knew they would be tough," Vesnina said. "Katarina is a very experienced doubles player and a great singles player as well, and Garcia is having a great season - we're very happy we stuck together and were able to get through it."

Both semifinals will take place on Thursday, with Hingis and Mirza playing against Raymond and Stosur on Stadium 1 and Makarova and Vesnina playing Jans-Ignacik and Klepac on Stadium 2.

Combined, the eight semifinalists have 41 Grand Slam titles between them. Hingis has the most Grand Slams with 16 (five singles, nine doubles and two mixed). Raymond is in second place with 11 (six doubles and five mixed) followed by Stosur (six), Makarova and Mirza (three each) and Vesnina (two).</Article>
    <Category>Tennis</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>INDIAN WELLS THURSDAY: UNUSUAL SUSPECTS
The final two semifinal spots at the BNP Paribas Open will be decided on Thursday and Chris Oddo gives his take on the two match-ups.
Published March 19, 2015 12:10

Indian Wells Thursday: Unusual Suspects Jelena Jankovic
INDIAN WELLS, CA, USA - The final two semifinal spots at the BNP Paribas Open will be decided on Thursday as Jelena Jankovic meets qualifier Lesia Tsurenko and then defending champion Flavia Pennetta takes on a revived Sabine Lisicki.

Thursday, Quarterfinals

Stadium 1
[18] Jelena Jankovic (SRB # 21) vs. [Q] Lesia Tsurenko (UKR #85)
Head-to-head: First meeting
Key Stat: After losing her first five matches against the Top 10, Tsurenko has won two in succession this week at Indian Wells. 
Former champion Jelena Jankovic is suddenly surging. The Serb, who now calls herself a "California girl," has won three straight three-setters in the desert to reach her first quarterfinal of the season. Her opponent, surprise quarterfinalist Lesia Tsurenko, has logged even more court time, winning two qualifying matches before reeling off four straight main draw wins, including three consecutive three-setters and two straight wins over Top 10 players. But will Tsurenko, who tweaked her ankle badly during her upset of Eugenie Bouchard on Tuesday, have enough gas in the tank for another upset? It will be a big ask against an in-form Jankovic, who owns a 21-12 record at Indian Wells, including two semifinals and a title.

[15] Flavia Pennetta (ITA #16) vs. [24] Sabine Lisicki (GER #30)
Head-to-head: First meeting 
Key Stat: Pennetta has now won nine straight matches at Indian Wells.
Both players found themselves awash in tears during highly emotional round of 16 battles on Tuesday. Pennetta would later tell reporters she was feeling overwhelmed, but her emotions didn't stop her from courageously fighting past Maria Sharapova in three sets to keep hopes of a BNP Paribas Open title defense alive. Lisicki cried for joy after defeating Caroline Garcia on Tuesday, and it seems as though the black cloud that has been hovering over the German in the form of a 1-6 start to 2015 has finally lifted.

With both players feeling untethered, and their darkest day behind them, expect some impassioned tennis in this first-time meeting of tour veterans.</Article>
    <Category>Tennis</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Pirri goes from scratch to scorer for Panthers
Thursday, 03.19.2015 / 3:00 AM / NHL Insider
By Alain Poupart - NHL.com Correspondent
CommentPrintE-mail
SUNRISE, Fla. -- This is how things have been going lately for Florida Panthers forward Brandon Pirri.

Forward Brad Boyes had just skated near the outside of the right circle when he dropped a pass near the top of the circle. Almost as quickly as Pirri received the pass, he released a wrist shot that whizzed between a couple of Montreal Canadiens players and rang in off the far post.

Just like that, Pirri had his 13th goal in 18 games, an Ovechkin-like pace that projects to 59 goals over a full NHL regular season.

"They're looking for a scorer in Florida," play-by-play voice Steve Goldstein said during the Panthers'  3-2 loss Tuesday. "He may be right here in this building. That guy."


NHL INSIDER

Senators' Hammond making history
By Adam Kimelman - NHL.com Deputy Managing Editor
Since his recall from the AHL, Andrew 'Hamburglar' Hammond has had a miraculous, historic run that has Ottawa back in playoff contention READ MORE ›
Sens' GM Murray fighting cancer, saving lives
Canucks honor Pat Quinn on St. Patrick's Day
Rutherford confident in Pens' playoff chances
MORE NHL INSIDER STORIES ›
When the Panthers play the Detroit Red Wings at BB&amp;T Center on Thursday (7:30 p.m. ET; NHLN-US), Pirri will be carrying his third three-game goal streak of the season.
As Florida tries to make the Stanley Cup Playoffs in the Eastern Conference, Pirri has been leading the way offensively. Not counting Dave Bolland's empty-net goal near the end of a 2-0 victory against the Carolina Hurricanes on Saturday, Pirri has scored three of the Panthers' past four goals.

"The coaches have put me in a position to produce," Pirri said. "I've got to prove them right by doing that, and also if I'm not producing I'm not going to be doing my part for the team to make the playoffs. It's just a matter that my teammates are setting me up well lately, and for me it's just trying to shoot everything."

Playing in 37 of their 70 games, Pirri ranks third on the Panthers with 16 goals, one behind Jimmy Hayes and eight behind Nick Bjugstad.

Pirri has missed games this season because of a concussion and a shoulder injury. And he had two stretches when he was a healthy scratch, in large part because of questions about his defensive ability.

The last stretch of healthy scratches came between mid-December and mid-January when Pirri sat 10 times in 15 games. These days, Pirri is too important offensively to sit.

"Everyone wants to be in the lineup every night," Pirri said. "For me, I was just trying to work hard and prove in practice that I could contribute. And when I did get my opportunity I just wanted to produce again. Now my mentality is I've got to produce again or else I'm not going to be in the lineup. I've been in and out all year and practically my whole career. For me, I'm trying to prove something every night."

Pirri had a stretch of six goals in eight games before he sustained a shoulder injury against the Anaheim Ducks on Feb. 10.

He missed nine games and returned 18 days later against the Buffalo Sabres in Jaromir Jagr's debut with the Panthers. Jagr and Pirri teamed up on the first power-play unit and the veteran kept telling Pirri to shoot the puck.

Pirri listened and scored twice in a 5-3 win, beginning his stretch of seven goals in nine games.

"We all know he's got a very good shot," forward Jonathan Huberdeau said. "And it's going in often. In the big games he shows up. On the power play we want to give him the puck because he's a real good shot. It's a little like [Alex] Ovechkin; even if the goalie is there, sometimes it's going to go in."

Pirri had nine shots on goal against Buffalo. He had 10 in a 3-2 loss to Montreal on Tuesday.

When the Florida Panthers play the Detroit Red Wings at BB&amp;T Center on Thursday, forward Brandon Pirri will be carrying his third three-game goal streak of the season. (Photo: Eliot J. Schechter/NHLI)
"We have a lot of playmakers that are putting me in position to score," Pirri said. "For me, it's just shoot the puck. I've had a lot of chances every night consistently. You don't have to think about it if you're missing one in the first [period], you're still going to have a lot of opportunities the rest of the game."

After Pirri, 23, joined the Panthers on March 2, 2014 in a trade with the Chicago Blackhawks for a third-round pick in the 2014 NHL Draft and a fifth-round pick in 2016, he scored seven goals in 21 games at the end of the season.
He also led the American Hockey League in scoring in 2012-13 with 75 points in 76 games.

"He's around the puck and he's a goal-scorer," Panthers coach Gerard Gallant said. "You can't teach that stuff. That's the way he's played his whole career. When he gets opportunities he makes the most of them. The goal the other night [against the New York Rangers] was just a quick shot, quick release. That's what it's all about: Put pucks at the net, and he likes to shoot the puck.

"He's working hard. He's just got to get bigger and stronger, like all the young players. But he's played a lot better and he's working hard. The key is keep scoring. That keeps coaches happy."</Article>
    <Category>IceHockey</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Kopitar, Gaborik searching for chemistry with Kings
Wednesday, 03.18.2015 / 3:00 AM / NHL Insider
By Curtis Zupke - NHL.com Correspondent
CommentPrintE-mail
LOS ANGELES -- Anze Kopitar and Marian Gaborik were briefly neighbors in the popular town of Manhattan Beach, Calif., when Kopitar was remodeling a home earlier this season. It's a natural fit: The two are cut from the same cloth, elite European players who enjoy anonymity in Southern California.


WEDNESDAY NIGHT RIVALRY
The Chicago Blackhawks visit the New York Rangers at 8 p.m. ET in the early game of a Wednesday Night Rivalry doubleheader. In the late game, the Los Angeles Kings continue their playoff push against the Anaheim Ducks at 10:30 p.m. ET.
Hawks vs. Rangers video | Kings vs. Ducks video
X-Factors: Saad, Talbot video | Toffoli, Lindholm video
Hawks-Rangers storylines | Tale of the Tape
Closer look: CHI, NYR play fast | Weekes
Richards eyes Cup | Lundqvist injury update
Kopitar, Gabby want more | Williams on push
video Join the Twitter conversation: #RivalryNight
But the buddy-movie notion of the two taking Kopitar's dog, Gustl, for a walk on the strand is slightly farfetched.
"We haven't gotten that far yet," Kopitar said.

That also might apply to their ongoing chemistry project this season for the Los Angeles Kings. After Gaborik and Kopitar clicked in last year's Stanley Cup Playoffs, the two will continue searching for that mesh when the Kings look to continue their climb up the Western Conference standings Wednesday at the Anaheim Ducks (10:30 p.m. ET; NBCSN).

Kopitar has 11 points in the past 14 games and is on pace to lead the Kings in scoring for the eighth straight season. Gaborik leads the Kings with 10 power-play goals and is second with 21 goals. The linemates, much like the Kings, are effective in stretches but haven't been able to find consistency.

Los Angeles coach Darryl Sutter judges players by the Kings' record with them in or out of the lineup. Los Angeles is 7-7-2 without Gaborik or Kopitar; Gaborik missed eight of the first 11 games of the season with an injury.

It speaks to Sutter's faith that he has kept Kopitar and Gaborik intact through hot and cold streaks. Jeff Carter and Tyler Toffoli also have remained linemates.

"You look at how much it's affected our record by those guys not being in the lineup and not playing together, it has a dramatic effect," Sutter said. "The story [of] Jeff and Tyler is a good story; they've carried us off and on all year. The reason is [Kopitar] and [Gaborik] not being consistent and productive together. [Gaborik] is leading our team in power-play goals, and we need him to do that. If you look at him, based on games played, he's a 30-40-goal scorer. So if we had him every game, we've been better off."

Sutter out of superstition was reluctant to talk about Kopitar and Gaborik staying healthy. Gaborik made the knock-on-wood gesture when asked about being able to stay in the lineup. He has a significant history of injuries, but the Kings signed him to a seven-year contract worth $34.1 million after they won their second Stanley Cup last June.

Gaborik mentioned Sutter's confidence, especially given that the coach is ruthless in his lineup changes.

"There's a trust that we can know that we get it done," Gaborik said. "We have to keep working on things and we have to keep getting it done. We've been able to click out there.

"[Anze is] a great possession player, and he can find people. You can use that to stay close to each other and use that for a give-and-go game."


Marian Gaborik

MARIAN GABORIK
RIGHT WING - LAK
GOALS: 21 | ASST: 17 | PTS: 38
SOG: 136 | +/-: 8
Even though Gaborik fit in with the Kings seamlessly after he arrived at the NHL Trade Deadline last season, he said it was beneficial to have a full offseason and season with them. In addition to the contract extension, he bought a home in Manhattan Beach in December (Kopitar is nearby) and can grab a cup of coffee without getting recognized.
"This year, it's been good that I started out right away in camp with these guys and just started from scratch," Gaborik said. "It feels good. Everyone believes we have a good team. We just need to get going here.

"You enjoy more when you win. Hopefully we can keep it that way."

Gaborik has gone long stretches without scoring, but had a six-game point streak and tied a career-high five-game goal-scoring streak this season.

"There's not much more that needs to be said about it," forward Justin Williams said. "He’s a world-class guy. He scores a lot of goals, and when he's on his game, he makes a lot of plays, and one thing a lot of people don’t know about [Gaborik] is they figure he scores a lot of goals from the high slot, but he scores a lot of goals from the dirty areas. He scores a lot of goals going to the net, poking at rebounds. And I think that's a misconception about him sometimes from the outside, that he's just a perimeter player. He's not."

Kopitar continues to establish himself among the top two-way centers in the NHL, which makes the games against Anaheim more interesting because the Ducks can counter with Ryan Getzlaf and Ryan Kesler.


Anze Kopitar

ANZE KOPITAR
CENTER - LAK
GOALS: 14 | ASST: 38 | PTS: 52
SOG: 107 | +/-: -2
The Ducks and Kings have great respect for each other but don't publicly pump up the rivalry as much as the local media wishes. Los Angeles has more immediate worries about making the playoffs, and Wednesday is their biggest obstacle yet.
"I guess in some ways it's kind of good to put yourselves in this position because you're forced to play your best hockey and then carry it over into the playoffs," Kopitar said. "We definitely want to go work at our game and be on our top of game come mid-April."

The Kings are 1-1-2 against the Ducks this season and have not won at Honda Center, where they won Game 7 of the Western Conference Second Round, the first playoff series between the teams.

They are in position to meet again, possibly in the first round, and Kopitar talked as if were a foregone conclusion.

"It's probably just going to add a little more fuel to the fire that we already have," he said. "It's not going to be anything new. It's just going to be another playoff series, obviously an intense one. Those are fun to play in."</Article>
    <Category>IceHockey</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Rutherford confident Penguins are ready for playoffs
Monday, 03.16.2015 / 5:45 PM / NHL Insider
By Shawn Roarke - Director, Editorial
CommentPrintE-mail
BOCA RATON, Fla.-- The Pittsburgh Penguins may have lost two home games in a 24-hour span last weekend, but general manager Jim Rutherford believes they are ready for the Stanley Cup Playoffs.

A shutout loss to the Boston Bruins in a Saturday matinee, and a 5-1 loss to the Detroit Red Wings in a nationally televised afternoon game on Sunday, sounded some alarm bells around a team which has struggled for consistency all season.

Rutherford, however, was not concerned when he arrived for the start of the spring installment of the NHL's general managers meetings. The Penguins are 39-20-10 and in third place in the Metropolitan Division, two points behind the New York Islanders with two games in hand. The Washington Capitals, which holds the first wild card into the Stanley Cup Playoffs from the Eastern Conference, are four points behind the Penguins.


GENERAL MANAGERS MEETINGS
NHL GMs gathered for three days of meetings in Boca Raton, Fla. Check out NHL.com's coverage:
GMs propose faceoff rule to increase offense
Watch: Rosen &amp; Dreger recap GM meetings 
NHL, union reps discuss change to OT format
Wings GM Holland  | Coyotes GM Maloney 
Rangers GM Sather: Lundqvist still needs time
"As long as we are healthy, we are ready for the [Stanley Cup] Playoffs and feel we can compete with anyone," Rutherford said Monday. "But, playoffs are playoffs; you get down to a series, especially the way it is now with parity, it can go either way. We're certainly prepared."
Health has been an issue all season for the Penguins. They have lost top-six forward Pascal Dupuis and young defenseman Olli Maatta to season-ending injuries. Twenty-four different players have dressed to fill their 12 forward spots and 13 different players have dressed to fill the six defensemen positions.

Yet, aside from the long-term injuries to Maatta and Dupuis, the Penguins were approaching full health as the weekend dawned.

"I was driving in the other day and I thought, 'Boy, we are going to be healthy for the first time and we're going to have a full lineup, other than the two guys that are out for the year,'" Rutherford said. "Then, I got there, found out [Sidney Crosby] wasn't playing and a few shifts in and [Evgeni] Malkin was out. Now from [Sunday], we have [Patric] Hornqvist out."

Crosby missed the game against the Bruins when he was a last-minute scratch because of illness. He returned Sunday, in part because Malkin was lost to injury in the first period of the game Saturday. On Sunday, Hornqvist was injured in the third period of the game against the Red Wings.

Rutherford said Monday that Malkin could miss 1-2 weeks and that Hornqvist would be out a week.

But the need to use more players and to be aggressive before and at the 2015 NHL Trade Deadline has transformed his team.

"Overall, we strengthened our defense, gave it more depth and more balance at the trade deadline and so as long as we can get healthy, I feel good about our team," Rutherford said. "We have more balance, we're deeper; our third and fourth line can contribute if our first and second get shut down.


Sidney Crosby

SIDNEY CROSBY
CENTER - PIT
GOALS: 23 | ASST: 48 | PTS: 71
SOG: 195 | +/-: 8
Plus, the Penguins still have Crosby, one of the best players in the game. Yes, Rutherford has heard the chorus of critics who look at Crosby's production and suggest he is playing at a subpar level.
"That's total nit-picking," Rutherford said. "There is nothing wrong with Sid."

The numbers may suggest otherwise. In 64 games, Crosby has 71 points. Crosby has played 70 or more games in four seasons during his career and has topped 100 points each time. Last season, he had 104 points in 80 games.

Yet the lack of production does not bother Rutherford. He believes his captain is doing more to help the Penguins be successful than he ever has.

"To me, his play has been as good as it's ever been, especially over the last month or so, and adjusting to [coach] Mike Johnston's system and what Mike is asking of him," Rutherford said. "From an overall team point of view and what needs to be done to be successful, he's made that adjustment and done it very well."

Johnston was Rutherford's choice to coach the Penguins, replacing Dan Bylsma, who was fired after the 2013-14 season. Johnston has changed the system under which the Penguins operate. It is based more on defensive responsibility than in the past. Rutherford said Crosby has bought in. He is coming back into his own zone more often and has agreed to let the stretch play to start transition fade from his game a bit.

"It's coming back into your own end, it's playing both ends of the rink, no cheating and playing the game the way it is meant to be played and he's bought into that," Rutherford said. "He's doing it very well. That trip out West and the California games, he was terrific in those games, played the way we need to play to win and be a good playoff team."</Article>
    <Category>IceHockey</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>LeBron James takes over No. 1 alone on Cavs assists list

POSTED: Mar 10, 2015 10:28 PM ET

AD
DALLAS (AP) — LeBron James has another Cavaliers record all to himself after getting his 4,207th assist in a Cleveland uniform.
James had an assist on James Jones' 3-pointer early in the second quarter against Dallas on Tuesday night, breaking a tie with Mark Price for the Cavs' career assists record.

James Dimes Jones
LeBron James passes Mark Price as the Cavaliers all-time assists leader.
Back in Cleveland after four seasons with the Miami Heat, James was already the Cavaliers' career leader for points, field goals made and attempted, 3-pointers made and attempted, free throws made and attempted, steals and minutes played. He played his first seven NBA seasons with the Cavs.
Only seven other players lead a franchise in points, assists and steals: Michael Jordan (Bulls), Kevin Garnett (Timberwolves), Reggie Miller (Pacers), Gary Payton (Sonics/Thunder), Randy Smith (Clippers), Isiah Thomas (Pistons) and Dwyane Wade (Heat). </Article>
    <Category>Basketball</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Pistons to keep F Miller rest of season

POSTED: Mar 11, 2015 11:11 PM ET

AD
OAKLAND, Calif. (AP) — Forward Quincy Miller will stick with the Detroit Pistons for the remainder of the season and have an opportunity to be part of summer league and then training camp.
Coach Stan Van Gundy said before Wednesday night's game at Golden State that Miller had earned the opportunity to have a long look. Miller signed his second 10-day contract with the Pistons on March 3.
Van Gundy said general manager Jeff Bower is working with Miller's agent to work out a contract that is not fully guaranteed.
While the Pistons have evaluated Miller in only a handful of practices, Van Gundy insists, "he's a guy with size and length and athletic ability and can shoot the ball, so he's somebody who we want to see. It's not a huge investment for us. He's a guy who has great potential to develop."
The 6-foot-9 Miller is averaging 2.8 points and 2.0 rebounds.</Article>
    <Category>Basketball</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Pacers' Hibbert sidelined vs. Knicks

POSTED: Mar 4, 2015 6:04 PM ET

AD
INDIANAPOLIS (AP) — Pacers center Roy Hibbert will not play Wednesday night against New York.
Coach Frank Vogel says he's giving the two-time All-Star extra rest during a week in which Indiana plays only one game in four days. Vogel says Hibbert is not injured and should start Friday night.
Ian Mahinmi will replace Hibbert with Lavoy Allen moving into the backup role.
Indiana (25-34) has won two straight and has pulled within a half-game of the No. 8 seed in the Eastern Conference standings.
Vogel would not say whether Paul George, Indiana's other two-time All-Star, could return the mid-March date George has established as his goal. The Pacers top player returned to practice last week and has gone through three or four full workouts but still has hurdles to clear, Vogel says.</Article>
    <Category>Basketball</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>HOUSTON — Rough. Tough. Physical. Contentious. Dirty.
"Yeah, it's like street ball," said James Harden. "You grew up playing games like that."
If Harden keeps growing up any faster, they're going to have to raise the rafters of Toyota Center just so he doesn't go straight through the roof.
He's scored more points in a game this season than he did Sunday. Grabbed more rebounds. Dished out more assists. Played more artistically.
But never been more ferocious, more driven.

Cavaliers vs. Rockets
James Harden scores 33 points and grabs eight rebounds as the Rockets defeat the Cavaliers in overtime.
You're damn right that 105-103 overtime win means more when it comes against LeBron James and the Cavaliers.
As messages go, this one couldn't have been delivered more emphatically if it had come wrapped around a brick and tossed through a plate glass window or attached to a flaming arrow.
"M-V-P."
While there may still be a horse race for the award this season, there's no doubt which thoroughbred is now galloping ahead of the field.
Less than 72 hours after James stated his case by outscoring Golden State's Stephen Curry 42-18 in a routine win by the Cavs, Harden provided his response.
James scored more points (37 to Harden's 33), but took far more shots (35 to 18) to get them. Playing without point guard Kyrie Irving, James controlled the ball like a yo-yo on a string and tried to do too much. Playing without center Dwight Howard, as he's done for much of the season, Harden simply opened his arms wide to embrace all of the things that had to be done.
"Every time you watch [Harden] play, you're watching history," Rockets Hall of Famer Hakeem Olajuwon had said a few hours before the tip. "He's doing something spectacular. Every night the best defensive player on the other team has to guard him and also the game plan of the other team is how to stop him. And he's still finding a way to be effective and giving them an opportunity to win every time. So he is definitely the MVP."
Harden could win the vote just on the way he's handled a season where Howard has sat on the shelf more than a potted plant and yet never allowed the Rockets to wilt with excuses or self pity.
He is the league's leading scorer because that's what the Rockets need him to be to have any chance with their current 41-18 record and No. 3 seed in the deep and dangerous Western Conference. He is his team's leading assist man because he's the one who knows how to get the most out of a supporting cast of role players. He's the one who lights their fire, keeps them moving forward and more often than not drags them across the finish line.
Lately Harden had been playing more the role of facilitator in the Rockets offense, but on Sunday he was the bowling ball that rolled down the alley and sent the pins flying.
There was the crossover dribble that left James rubber-legged as Harden juked left and then cruised right toward the hoop. There were the times he bull-rushed J.R. Smith to make it to the rim.
Most especially, there was the possession late in the third quarter when James and Tristan Thompson converged on a double-team to tie up Harden and force a jump ball. While James tried to use one arm to pin him to the floor, Harden lashed out with left leg and kicked King James in the family jewels. The kick drew a flagrant foul on Harden and then only a shrug.

Harden's Flagrant Foul
James Harden appears to kick LeBron James during the third quarter.
"We're growing as a team," Harden said. "Early in the season things got tough and we didn't know how to pull the situations out. Lately we've grown. We been believing in each other."
They're believing in each other because they believe in him and as the season gets later, the stakes get higher and the spotlight grows brighter.
People laughed last summer when Harden said he was the best player in the NBA. Now he gets to stand at the free-throw line with those "M-V-P! M-V-P!" chants as affirmation.
"Obviously, it's a great feeling," he said. "It's moments you dream of, especially since I know how hard I've worked to put myself in this situation. I just embrace and enjoy it."
He embraced the last seven minutes of the fourth quarter and overtime when the Cavs made their defensive adjustment and guarded him with James.
"I knew it was gonna come at some point," Harden said. "Of course, I always want it. An opportunity to go up against the best player in the world, you've got to take advantage of it."
It was a day when James not only missed 20 attempts from the field, but shot just 3-for-11 from the foul line and missed seven of his last eight free throws, including two with 4.2 seconds left in overtime that potentially could have won the game.

LeBron Misses Crucial Free Throws
LeBron misses two crucial free throws at the end of Sunday's game.
It was a game that would have fit right at home in June, dripping with importance and emotion, the kind Harden remembers from Oklahoma City and yearns to carry a team of his own through.
"Yeah, definitely, the intensity," he said. "Each possession counting. For both teams it was like a playoff game. We were prepared for it."
Rough. Tough. Physical. Contentious. Dirty. An MVP statement.
"Every game is a statement for me," Harden said. "I'm out here trying to prove myself."
Fran Blinebury has covered the NBA since 1977. You can e-mail him here and follow him on Twitter.
The views on this page do not necessarily reflect the views of the NBA, its clubs or Turner Broadcasting.</Article>
    <Category>Basketball</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Raptors' Williams back, Patterson out vs. Pelicans

POSTED: Feb 23, 2015 7:31 PM ET

AD
NEW ORLEANS (AP) — Toronto Raptors coach Dwane Casey says shooting guard Lou Williams is returning from a sprained ankle for Monday night's game against the Pelicans, while power forward Patrick Patterson is sitting out because of his sprained left knee.
Williams, who averages 15.4 points, has missed only one game with his injury, a loss in Houston on Saturday night.
Patterson's injury occurred during last Friday night's victory in Atlanta. He played the following night against the Rockets, finishing with five points and four rebounds in a little less than 24 minutes.
The Raptors then had listed Patterson, who averages 8.5 points and 5.5 rebounds, as questionable for Monday night's game, and he was ruled out a little more than an hour before tipoff.</Article>
    <Category>Basketball</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>HOUSTON — The trade deadline has always been like a bowl of potato chips sitting in front of Daryl Morey.
Go ahead, try to resist just one.
So when the Rockets wheeler-dealer general manager shuffled the deck with the clock ticking down last week nobody was even a bit surprised.
That is, nobody who wasn't expecting a game-changer.
The truth is, in the eight seasons that Morey has been polishing up his considerable reputation as a go-for-broke house-flipper in Houston, each February has brought little more than rearranging the patio furniture.
That is not to dismiss all of the maneuvering as inconsequential in the long run, since the likes of Jordan Hill for Derek Fisher (waived) in 2012 and Patrick Patterson, Toney Douglas and Cole Aldrich for Thomas Robinson and Francisco Garcia in 2013 did come to provide critical salary flexibility that allowed the Rockets to go out and land James Harden and Dwight Howard.
But a fan base that will always measure every eye-batting flirtation against the sweetheart 1995 Valentine's Day pursuit and capture of hometown hero Clyde Drexler that delivered a second consecutive championship, tiptoes longingly toward each annual trade deadline hoping for the kind of big, hot smooch that brings stars to your eyes.
Instead they get a 22-year-old rookie K.J. McDaniels and a 37-year-old point guard Pablo Prigioni and wonder how that brings the Rockets any closer to the first title — and only the second playoff series win — since Drexler retired back there in the last millennium.
The answer, of course, is that it doesn't. And the plain fact is that might not have changed significantly even if the Morey had been able to convince Goran Dragic that a return to Houston wouldn't have stunted his career.
Dragic had trust issues. He didn't trust his role in the Rockets' offense would be much different than the one he chafed at in Phoenix with the ball so often in the hands of Harden. He didn't trust that Morey wouldn't turn around and ship him right back out of town if a shinier bauble presented itself.
Maybe Dragic didn't also trust that Howard would eventually return to the lineup this season as the dominant inside force at both ends of the floor that the Rockets need to have anything more than championship fever dreams.

The Starters: No Dwight, No Problem?
Dwight Howard is likely out for "weeks", does this spell disaster for the Rockets?
While good health is certainly of primary concern in every corner of the league from San Antonio to Miami to Cleveland to Portland, the Rockets have reason to fret. Now 29 and in his 11th NBA season, Howard no longer flies through slam dunk contests wearing a Superman cape and is no longer an iron man in the lineup. Howard missed a total of 25 games in his career in the nine years before arriving in Houston. Monday night was the 24th game he's missed this season, one that has already had Howard undergoing platelet rich plasma therapy and a bone marrow aspirate injection for a troublesome right knee with recurrent swelling and pain.
The Rockets and their medical staff are hopeful that Howard can be back on the court by late March or early April, providing time to be in shape for the playoffs. Without him, there is no real path to getting out of the Western Conference even in a year when the landscape appears wide open with no clear-cut favorite.
The other question is: with the MVP candidate Harden playing spectacularly as he leads the league in scoring and consistently carrying the team on his back to a 38-18 record and a current spot as the No. 3 seed in the West, could the Rockets negotiate their way through the minefield even with Howard?
Harden's second triple-double of the season in Monday night came as the Timberwolves pushed Houston to the end and squeezed another 39 minutes out of him. Harden is averaging just under 37 heavy-duty minutes a game and the effects of that load could show up just when the Rockets will need him most in the postseason.

Inside The NBA: James Harden
Here's an extended look at Rachel Nichols' sitdown intervew with the Rockets' James Harden.
There was a reason why Morey and the Rockets pursued Chris Bosh so hard last summer: the belief that they needed a third All-Star level piece to their puzzle. While the trade-off of Chandler Parsons for Trevor Ariza has made the defense better, the offense is not as potent.
Donatas Motiejunas has made a case for himself to be included in Most Improved Player of the Year talk and the addition of Corey Brewer has provided speed, athleticism and energy off the bench, but there remains a glaring hole at point guard. For all the snarling intensity that Patrick Beverley brings on defense, his shooting has often been horrid and he's no better at delivering the ball into the paint.
The Rockets are simply too dependent on Harden to do too much, even with a healthy Howard. That's where Dragic or another upgrade could have fit, allowing Beverley to take his rightful coming off the bench as a change-of-pace, in-your-face backup. Now they're left cornering the market on 37-year-old reserves in Prigioni and Jason Terry.
It's been fun, sometimes breathtaking, watching Harden blossom and take his game up another notch to the next level. But there remains real doubt that it's gotten the Rockets ultimately closer to the goal. If there was ever a time to do more than shuffle around furniture, this was it.
Fran Blinebury has covered the NBA since 1977. You can e-mail him here and follow him on Twitter.
The views on this page do not necessarily reflect the views of the NBA, its clubs or Turner Broadcasting. </Article>
    <Category>Basketball</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Trophy, playoff races among questions remaining
Monday, 03.16.2015 / 3:18 PM / NHL Insider
By Dan Rosen - NHL.com Senior Writer
CommentPrintE-mail
There are fewer than 200 games remaining in the 2014-15 NHL regular season and the only race remotely close to being decided is the one for first place in the Pacific Division. The Anaheim Ducks have a 13-point lead.

The rest of the playoff chases and scoring races are still up for grabs. Home-ice advantage is on the line. Players are trying secure their candidacy for postseason awards. Ten teams are within eight points of the lead for the Presidents' Trophy.

So much still has to be decided and yet the days are quickly ticking off the calendar. So many questions still have to be answered, but why wait until April 11, the final day of the regular season, when all 30 teams are in action? Why can't we just answer the hot questions now?

Here are 15 important questions heading into the homestretch of the season, with some educated guesswork for the answers:

1. WHO WILL WIN THE PRESIDENTS' TROPHY?


NHL INSIDER

Senators' Hammond making history
By Adam Kimelman - NHL.com Deputy Managing Editor
Since his recall from the AHL, Andrew 'Hamburglar' Hammond has had a miraculous, historic run that has Ottawa back in playoff contention READ MORE ›
Sens' GM Murray fighting cancer, saving lives
Canucks honor Pat Quinn on St. Patrick's Day
Rutherford confident in Pens' playoff chances
MORE NHL INSIDER STORIES ›
There are two teams tied with 95 points, but the New York Rangers have the lead because of their games played (68) and regulation/overtime victories (41). They have three games in hand on the Anaheim Ducks, who also have 95 points.
The Montreal Canadiens, St. Louis Blues and Nashville Predators and Predators are also front and center in this race, but there are now seven teams within five points of each other.

Best guess: New York Rangers

The Rangers the most games remaining (14) of any team. They have seven games left at Madison Square Garden, where they're 22-7-5 this season. They play seven games against teams that aren't in a playoff position entering play Monday.

The Blues (93 points) have the next most games remaining (13) of the teams within three points of first, but they play seven on the road and have to face the Chicago Blackhawks two times as well as the Detroit Red Wings, Pittsburgh Penguins, Vancouver Canucks, Calgary Flames and Minnesota Wild.

2. WHO WILL WIN THE CENTRAL DIVISION?

The Predators, Blues and Blackhawks are within five points of each other. The Blues and Predators are tied with 93 points.

Best guess: St. Louis Blues

The Blues have two games in hand on the Predators. They could come in handy. The Predators have an easier April, but the Blues play six games in April and that should make the difference.

3. WHO WILL WIN THE ATLANTIC DIVISION?

The race is between the Canadiens and Tampa Bay Lightning, though the Red Wings are not out of it yet. Montreal and Tampa Bay are separated by two points. The Canadiens have a game in hand. The Lightning and Canadiens play twice more this season, so there's a good chance that this race can be determined in those head-to-head matchups.

The Lightning play at home against Montreal on Monday; the Canadiens are home against Tampa Bay on March 30.

Best guess: Montreal Canadiens

Carey Price is the difference in this race. He has played so well of late that he has solidified his Hart Trophy candidacy. If the Canadiens can do a better job in front of him in their final 13 games Price will carry Montreal to the division title.

Tampa Bay takes a hit by losing forward Ondrej Palat and defenseman Braydon Coburn to injuries.

4. WHO WILL WIN THE METROPOLITAN DIVISION?

The Rangers, New York Islanders, and Penguins are within seven points of each other. The Washington Capitals are 11 points off the lead in fourth.

The only head-to-head matchup left between the top three teams is April 10, when the Islanders play the Penguins at Consol Energy Center. The Rangers still have two games against Washington.

Best guess: New York Rangers

The Rangers are pegged as the Presidents' Trophy winners in the answer to the first question, so obviously that means they would win the Metropolitan Division as well. They are 18-5-1 against Metropolitan Division opponents this season. The Islanders are 19-5-1 vs. the division.

5. WILL THE LOS ANGELES KINGS MAKE THE PLAYOFFS?

The Kings are one point behind the Winnipeg Jets for the second wild card in the Western Conference with 14 games remaining. They are two points behind the Flames for third place in the Pacific Division. They three points behind the Canucks for second. It's that close.

Best guess: Yes

Despite what appears to be a tough schedule, Los Angeles not only will make the playoffs, it will finish second in the Pacific Division. The Kings will overtake the Canucks and Flames to finish behind the Ducks.

It won't be easy, though. The Kings have to get through a tough six-game stretch that includes a home game against the Ducks on Wednesday followed by a five-game road trip featuring three games in the New York-New Jersey area. They play the Edmonton Oilers twice in April.

But the Kings have done this before in the regular season only to come out just fine. They won the Stanley Cup as the eighth seed in 2012 and had to win three Game 7s on the road last season before winning the Stanley Cup again.

6. WHO WILL BE THE WILD-CARD TEAMS IN THE WESTERN CONFERENCE?

Let's start by eliminating the Kings from this answer because we just said they're going to finish second in the Pacific Division.

The top candidates for the two wild cards in the Western Conference are the Wild, Flames, Canucks, San Jose Sharks and Winnipeg Jets. The Blackhawks could still drop and the Avalanche could climb, but the likelihood of either happening is slim with the amount of games remaining and the potential for three-point games.

Best guess: Wild and Flames

Minnesota will get in despite having arguably the toughest schedule left of any Western Conference team, including two games against the Blues, two against the Predators, and one each against the Blackhawks, Rangers, Kings, Capitals, Islanders, Red Wings, Flames and Jets.

The Wild have been getting excellent goaltending from Devan Dubnyk and they're among the best teams in the Western Conference at suppressing shot attempts and controlling possession. But they also showed they can win when giving up a lot of shots, as they did in a 3-1 win against the Blues on Saturday, when they were outshot 42-19 but won because of Dubnyk.

The Flames are among the worst teams in the NHL at suppressing shot attempts and controlling possession, but whatever they're doing seems to be working because they are still in the race in spite of the fact that they trail early in most games and lost captain Mark Giordano, a Norris Trophy favorite, for the season.

The Jets should not be discounted and watch out for the Sharks, who are playing better of late. Inconsistency has been an issue for San Jose, though.

7. WHO WILL WIN THE ART ROSS TROPHY?


John Tavares

JOHN TAVARES
CENTER - NYI
GOALS: 33 | ASST: 39 | PTS: 72
SOG: 239 | +/-: 4
In all likelihood there won't be a 100-point player for the first time in a full regular season (non-lockout year) since 2003-04, before the red line was taken out, but there are a number of players jockeying for position.
Islanders captain John Tavares has the lead with 72 points. Capitals captain Alex Ovechkin, who won the scoring race in 2007-08, and center Nicklas Backstrom have 71 points. Penguins captain Sidney Crosby, the winner last season and a two-time NHL regular-season scoring champ, has 70 points.

Pittsburgh center Evgeni Malkin, Philadelphia Flyers right wingJakub Voracek, Blues left wing Vladimir Tarasenko and Lightning center Tyler Johnson are also in the mix.

Best guess: Sidney Crosby

This will only happen if Crosby doesn't miss any more time. He sat out the game Saturday because he was ill. Crosby has two things going for him, other than his world-class talent: 1) He is red-hot with 13 points in his past 10 games; 2) The Penguins have 13 games remaining, one more than the Capitals and two more than the Islanders.

Assuming Crosby plays the rest of the way, he could finish with 85 points based on his current pace. It'll be just enough to edge out the field. It will also be the fewest points for a scoring champ in a full NHL season in the modern era (post expansion).

8. WHO WILL WIN THE ROCKET RICHARD TROPHY?

This race is not decided, but it's getting close. There are three legitimate candidates in Ovechkin, Rangers forward Rick Nash and Lightning captain Steven Stamkos, but there is one overwhelming favorite.

Best guess: Alex Ovechkin

It's hardly a guess at this point. Ovechkin has a six-goal lead on Nash for first in the NHL. Ovechkin has 45 goals, including 21 on the power play.

Ovechkin will win this race because of his prowess on the power play. Nash has only five power play goals. Stamkos has 37 goals, including 10 on the power play.

9. WILL OVECHKIN SCORE 50?

Ovechkin has 29 goals in his past 34 games, including 14 goals on the power play. He has scored at least 50 goals in five of his eight full seasons in the League (not including 2012-13).

Best guess: Yes

Ovechkin has 12 games to get five goals. By his current pace he'll crack 50 before the end of the month, maybe even before the end of the week.

He has scored 11 goals in 20 games against the 11 opponents remaining on Washington's schedule. He surprisingly has no goals in three games against the Carolina Hurricanes. He had 27 goals in 57 games against the Hurricanes coming into the season.

10. WHO WILL WIN THE HART TROPHY?

Like the Art Ross Trophy race, this one is wide open with no absolute favorite. The same players vying for the scoring title are up for considering for the MVP trophy, but they're competing against a goalie who might be running away with the Vezina Trophy.

Best guess: Carey Price

Whoever thinks goalies can't win the Hart Trophy because they have their own trophy hasn't watched Price carry the Canadiens this season. Price will be the first goalie to win the Hart Trophy since Jose Theodore, yes of the Canadiens, took home the hardware in 2002.

Montreal was 23rd in the NHL in shots on goal against per game (30.5) and 23rd in shot attempts percentage (48.60 SAT), but they are in the running for the Presidents' Trophy. The reason is Price, who leads the NHL with 38 wins, a .936 save percentage and a 1.91 goals-against average.

11. WILL HENRIK LUNDQVIST RETURN BEFORE THE PLAYOFFS?


Henrik Lundqvist

HENRIK LUNDQVIST
GOALIE - NYR
RECORD: 25-11-3
GAA: 2.25 | SVP: .922
Lundqvist hasn't played since Feb. 2 because of a vascular injury sustained when he was hit in the throat by a shot on Jan. 31 against the Carolina Hurricanes. Lundqvist said he snapped his neck back so hard that he partially tore a blood vessel and could have suffered a stroke if he kept playing.
The Rangers have continued to win without Lundqvist. Cam Talbot and an offense that scored 39 goals in a 10-game stretch have been the difference in the Rangers' soaring up the standings to the top spot. Mackenzie Skapski has two wins against the Sabres. The Rangers are 15-2-3 without Lundqvist.

Best guess: Yes

Lundqvist has been skating on his own and taking low shots from goalie coach Benoit Allaire as part of his rehab. He is staying in shape so he can return as soon as he gets medical clearance from his doctors.

Lundqvist's return has nothing to do with how he feels and everything to do with what the doctors tell him. As a result it's impossible to put a timeline on his return, but Lundqvist is preparing as if he is planning to return before the playoffs.

12. WHO WILL FINISH 30TH?

The race at the bottom of the standings is intriguing too, because the prize at the end of a bad season could be a generational player. Connor McDavid and Jack Eichel are expected to be the first and second picks in the 2015 NHL Draft. They are expected to have immediate impacts.

The team that finishes 30th team has a 20 percent chance of securing the first pick in the draft via the 2015 NHL Draft Lottery, but it can't fall further than the No. 2 pick, meaning it is guaranteed the opportunity to select one of McDavid or Eichel.

The top three candidates are the Buffalo Sabres, Edmonton Oilers, and Arizona Coyotes.

Best guess: Buffalo Sabres

The Sabres are 30th and are four points clear of the 29th-place Oilers and six points clear of the 28th-place Coyotes. They have a game in hand on both the Oilers and Coyotes. The decisions Buffalo made prior to the 2015 NHL Trade Deadline were geared toward improving its draft position.

Buffalo is 6-27-4 in its past 37 games. The Sabres went 0-12-0 in January.

13. WILL THE PANTHERS OR SENATORS GET A WILD CARD?

The Boston Bruins lost Sunday to the Washington Capitals but have a hold on the second wild card in the Eastern Conference with 82 points and 13 games left. Ottawa is five points back with 14 games remaining. Florida is six points out with 13 games to play.
The Panthers have the advantage of playing three games against the Bruins. Two of those three games are in Florida, where the Panthers are 16-10-7 this season. They play their final five games at home.

Ottawa has one game remaining each against Washington and Boston, and the advantage of playing the Maple Leafs three times. The Senators also have two games left against the Rangers and one each against the Red Wings, Lightning, and Penguins.

Best guess: Neither team gets a wild card

The Bruins have been playing much better of late and have built a big enough cushion to secure their spot. Odds are they won't lose three games to the Panthers, so even if they get two out of six points available against Florida, or split the difference and get three, they'll still be in fine shape. Boston also has games left against Buffalo, Toronto and Carolina.

Washington, two points ahead of the Bruins with 84, hardly is set but the Capitals have a big enough cushion on the Senators and Panthers that getting in shouldn't be a problem as long as their slump doesn't continue.

14. WILL ROBERTO LUONGO WIN FOUR MORE GAMES TO REACH 400 WINS?


Roberto Luongo

ROBERTO LUONGO
GOALIE - FLA
RECORD: 23-16-11
GAA: 2.37 | SVP: .921
Luongo has been out since sustaining a shoulder injury on March 3. He is stuck on 396 wins for his career. There's a chance he could play Sunday against the Rangers.
Best guess: Yes

Luongo did not return Sunday. When he does, he'll likely be asked to play every game until the Panthers either clinch a playoff spot or get eliminated from contention. That means he could play the remaining 13 games on the schedule, which gives him enough time to win four more games. Florida has two back-to-back sets remaining.

15. WHO WILL WIN THE ROOKIE SCORING RACE?

It has come down to Filip Forsberg of the Predators and Johnny Gaudreau of the Flames.

Forsberg has been the leader and favorite for most of the season, but Gaudreau pulled even in the race Friday with a three-point game against the Maple Leafs. They each have 53 points. Forsberg has four points in his past 16 games. Gaudreau has nine points in his past seven games.

Best guess: Johnny Gaudreau

Gaudreau has gotten hot at the right time while Forsberg has cooled considerably. Gaudreau also has 13 games left; Forsberg has 11.</Article>
    <Category>IceHockey</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Sabres' Larsson, Varone shining in expanded roles
Monday, 03.16.2015 / 1:44 PM / NHL Insider
By Joe Yerdon - NHL.com Correspondent
CommentPrintE-mail
BUFFALO -- Following the NHL Trade Deadline on March 2, the Buffalo Sabres' lineup took on a drastically different look. It also provided a big opportunity to a pair of young centers.

Johan Larsson and Philip Varone have seen playing time in Buffalo before this season, but after two trades at the deadline that saw forwards Brian Flynn and Torrey Mitchell sent to the Montreal Canadiens, as well as a lower-body injury sustained by All-Star center Zemgus Girgensons, Larsson and Varone were recalled from the Rochester Americans of the American Hockey League to fill those holes. Now they’re the Sabres' top two centers heading into their game Monday against the Washington Capitals (7 p.m. ET, NBCSN, SN1).


NHL INSIDER

Senators' Hammond making history
By Adam Kimelman - NHL.com Deputy Managing Editor
Since his recall from the AHL, Andrew 'Hamburglar' Hammond has had a miraculous, historic run that has Ottawa back in playoff contention READ MORE ›
Sens' GM Murray fighting cancer, saving lives
Canucks honor Pat Quinn on St. Patrick's Day
Rutherford confident in Pens' playoff chances
MORE NHL INSIDER STORIES ›
Larsson hasn't been a stranger to the Sabres lineup this season. He's been in Buffalo since he was recalled Feb. 15, but he was playing on the third and fourth lines. Now he's between Matt Moulson and Tyler Ennis on the first line.
"It's a great opportunity. I can't ask for anything more," Larsson said. "I've just got to show it every day and work hard. If you play with those guys you have to work your [butt] off and show them you want to play with them."

Coach Ted Nolan moved Larsson to the first line March 7 against the Capitals. The Sabres lost that game 6-1 at Verizon Center, but Larsson scored Buffalo's goal. Larsson said that game made him feel like his time had come to prove what he could do.

"I actually [felt like a first-line player] when I lined up against [Nicklas] Backstrom," Larsson said. "I have to focus every shift if you play against top players in this League."

In his second game as the No. 1 center, Larsson had a goal and two assists in a 4-3 shootout loss to the Toronto Maple Leafs on March 11. The offensive output is enough to get attention, but there's always more to it than what the numbers say.

"You've got to try to do something to separate yourself and give yourself an opportunity to stay in the NHL," Nolan said Friday. "One thing I liked about [Larsson] is he separated a lot of defensemen from the puck with his body positioning. He moved his legs offensively as well as defensively. He was gritty, he got [Maple Leafs defenseman Dion] Phaneuf a couple times, rattled him, by being a pain in the rear out there. Those are all the things you do to separate yourself."

Larsson's ice time has gone up each of the three games he's played on Buffalo's top line, topping out at a season-high 18:19 in a 2-0 loss to the New York Rangers on Saturday.


Johan Larsson

JOHAN LARSSON
LEFT WING - BUF
GOALS: 3 | ASST: 4 | PTS: 7
SOG: 24 | +/-: 2
"He's been playing great," Ennis said. "He's been electric. He's been hard-working. He's been fun to play with. He's been our best player, I think, the last couple games. This is a great opportunity for him and he knows he's trying to seize the opportunity right now. You don't get these opportunities very often and he's playing amazing and we need him to continue playing that way."
Varone's spot on the second line has him playing with Marcus Foligno and Sabres captain Brian Gionta. Varone initially was on the first line and had a goal and an assist in a 3-2 loss to the Ottawa Senators on March 6. After that game Varone swapped with Larsson and has found chemistry as well as a reunion.

"Me and Marcus played together in Rochester almost for a year and a half straight and I like playing with him," Varone said. "He's a big body, smart, can skate. [Gionta], you can learn from him in every aspect of the game. He's a smaller-statured guy, so he's someone I can look up to and take stuff from. It seems like he's always in the right place at the right time. He's never really getting hit and always moving his feet and I'm just taking little things from him throughout the game, asking him little questions, so it's just been awesome."

Like Larsson, Varone has had a few opportunities in the past to play in Buffalo. He played nine games last season and seven games this season in January before being sent back to Rochester. Since the trade deadline he has been a full-time player counted on to produce.


Philip Varone

PHILIP VARONE
CENTER - BUF
GOALS: 3 | ASST: 1 | PTS: 4
SOG: 17 | +/-: -6
"He has a lot of poise out there," Gionta said. "He knows the game; he's in the right position. But when he gets it he can make plays. We've seen some of the games he's had; he's made some great plays. He's gotten to those scoring areas away from the puck. Getting to those open areas is always a thing you've got to learn and he's done a good job of that."
The points haven't come in big numbers yet for Varone, but that's not what he's focused on to prove himself in the NHL.

"[It's about] just being more aware on the defensive side of the puck," Varone said. "In the AHL I could kind of get away with that a little bit. I think I've been really working on that. In the AHL I probably take about 25 to 30 faceoffs a game, whereas here I take 16 or 17 so I've been bearing down more on that.

"It's just the little things. And once that starts ironing itself out and becomes second nature the offense will become second nature after that, which is kind of more what I'm going to try and bring. But at the same time you have to be responsible defensively."</Article>
    <Category>IceHockey</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Flames' Gaudreau scores twice to join select company
Thursday, 03.12.2015 / 11:45 AM / Top Performer
NHL.com
CommentPrintE-mail
Johnny Gaudreau's heroics helped the Calgary Flames rally to another victory Wednesday while keeping them firmly in the race to make the Stanley Cup Playoffs.

The rookie forward scored twice as part of five unanswered goals by the Flames en route to a 6-3 win against the Anaheim Ducks. The victory stretched Calgary's point streak to five straight games (4-0-1).


Johnny Gaudreau

JOHNNY GAUDREAU
LEFT WING - CGY
GOALS: 18 | ASST: 32 | PTS: 50
SOG: 133 | +/-: 6
Gaudreau had a goal waved off 39 seconds after forward Matt Stajan opened the scoring for the Flames but scored the equalizer at 15:25 of the first period when he received a pass from forward Josh Jooris and connected on a backhand that went off each post before going over the line. Gaudreau's second goal came on the power play at 13:59 of the second when he finished a give-and-go with defenseman Dennis Wideman.
"Everyone's stepping up here, whether it's a defenseman or a forward, first line or fourth line," Gaudreau said. "It's great to see that too when we're coming down the playoff stretch here. It's going to help us in the long run."

Gaudreau's fourth multigoal game extended his point streak to a career-high five games (3-3-6). He is the first Flames rookie to score 50 points since Jarome Iginla in 1996-97.

"It's pretty special for me to be part of something like that. Jarome Iginla, I grew up watching him," Gaudreau said. "He's been so successful. It's exciting to be a part of something like that. I always dreamed about playing in the NHL. I'm pretty fortunately to be playing with [Jiri Hudler] and [Sean Monahan], who have really helped me out here all season long."

The third-place Flames (37-25-5) have 79 points, one behind the Vancouver Canucks in the Pacific Division and two ahead of the Los Angeles Kings.</Article>
    <Category>IceHockey</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>HODGKINSON: WATSON'S NEWFOUND BELIEF
A little help from a former Grand Slam finalist has helped British No.1 Heather Watson raise her game to a new level.
Published March 17, 2015 12:12

Hodgkinson: Watson's Newfound Belief Heather Watson
Suddenly, there's nothing more fashionable in British tennis than working with a coaching consultant who has appeared on reality television. Who knows, you might even end up beating an elite, Top 10 opponent, a past Grand Slam finalist who also has a former reality TV contestant among her support staff?

In the men's game, Andy Murray has disclosed he is to have a trial week with Jonas Bjorkman, who is currently on a Swedish ballroom dancing show, with a view to hiring him as an assistant coach. Meanwhile, Britain's leading female player, Heather Watson, recently spent some time on the practice court in London with Greg Rusedski, whose retirement has included pirouetting in skates on 'Dancing on Ice'. Collaborating with Rusedski, a former US Open finalist, clearly hasn't done Watson any harm at all (though Watson's primary coach remains Diego Veronelli, an Argentine who has been in her corner for more than a year). The Channel Islander achieved the biggest win of her career at the Indian Wells Tennis Garden when she defeated Agnieszka Radwanska, a past Wimbledon finalist, who has linked up with Martina Navratilova, a winner of 18 Grand Slam singles titles, and once the runner-up on British television's 'I'm a Celebrity: Get Me Out of Here'.

One spring at the French Open, Watson used the most memorable of phrases to describe her emotions after a victory; she spoke of "being in Happy Land", and you can be sure that she was back there again after a first victory over a Top 10 opponent. All 11 of Watson's past encounters with opponents of that caliber had ended in defeat, and some of them had been very one-sided indeed. On one previous occasion that Watson had played Radwanska, the Pole had "wiped" the Briton off the court (that's Watson's choice of verb). This time it was different, and Watson - who had beaten Germany's Julia Goerges and Italy's Camila Giorgi in her first two matches of the tournament - won in straight sets to go through into the last 16 of the BNP Paribas Open. "I knew I had the tennis in me, but I needed the belief," Watson said of her first win over a Top 10 opponent, and where has she found that self-confidence?

It's plain that Watson feels as though working with Veronelli has benefited her game - and she spoke warmly about the South American after beating Radwanska - but Rusedski's involvement is interesting. After the best possible start to the season, with Watson scoring a title in Hobart in Tasmania to become the first British woman since the 1980s to win two WTA tournaments, everything went quiet for a couple of months. She was beaten in the opening round of the Australian Open and in Dubai, and though she made some progress in the qualifying competition in Doha, by winning a match, she couldn't make it all the way through to the tournament proper.

It was on returning from Qatar, Watson's agent told wtatennis.com, that the 22-year-old worked with Rusedski in London. "It was Diego and Heather's idea," Watson's agent said, "and Greg was on board to help."

During his own playing career, Rusedski was known for his gargantuan serve, and, judging from Watson's performances in California, it does appear as though there is a little more pop on her delivery (though it should be noted that Veronelli has also been trying to add some power to Watson's serve). Clearly, Watson and Rusedski enjoyed the time they had together on the practice court, as there is a decent chance that they will reunite again later in the year. "Diego is still Heather's primary coach," said Watson's agent, "but Greg may help for more days later in the year as a consultant."

With Laura Robson's long absence with a wrist injury (she has withdrawn from the qualifying competition for Miami, where she had been planning on playing her first competitive tennis for more than a year), Watson is the only British woman in the Top 100. Watson, whose ranking fell outside the Top 150 last year as she worked her way back from a bout of glandular fever, recently told me how many people in tennis didn't think she would make it this far: "When I was in the juniors, a lot of people didn't think I would win a junior Grand Slam [she was the girls' champion at the US Open]. And then in the seniors, a lot of people didn't think I would make the Top 100. A lot of people didn't think I would make the Top 50. So a lot of people didn't think I would ever be here now."

Until Watson, who ever heard of a world-class tennis player from Guernsey? Currently ranked 43, she has ambitions of being among the 32 seeds at a Grand Slam for the first time - her victory over Radwanska demonstrated why that's an achievable aim.</Article>
    <Category>Tennis</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>BNP PARIBAS OPEN HONORS WTA ICONS
Dozens of tennis legends gathered in Indian Wells to honor two women who helped change the face of women's tennis.
Published March 16, 2015 12:12

BNP Paribas Open Honors WTA Icons Peachy Kellmeyer
Once upon a time in the '70s the WTA had only just begun. Yes, there were players, stars like Billie Jean King and Chris Evert captivating increasing numbers of fans all across the globe (well, mostly in those days in North America). There were sponsors, most notably Virginia Slims. There was increasing exposure, including national television coverage on CBS.

But how was this tour going to be run? Now that the players were in charge of their destiny and the game was no longer in the hands of genteel patricians based in clubs, what kind of rules would govern everything from the operation of tournaments to etiquette, entry fees, media obligations, the calendar and all the hundreds of small and big questions that comprise a professional sport?

Sunday night at the BNP Paribas Open, dozens of WTA notables of the last six decades, including Martina Navratilova, Chris Evert and Tracy Austin, gathered to honor two women who often had the answers - or at least attempted to find the answers - to these questions. The occasion: the fifth annual Annalee Thurston Award Presentation (presented by esurance). Thurston, who died in 2007, was an integral part of the women's game for 35 years, most notably pioneering the startup tour's communications function.

Sunday's event was a fundraiser for the scholarship created in her name at the Warsaw Sports Marketing Center at the University of Oregon. The event also honors a notable from the world of women's sports. This year's honoree was one of the WTA's own, Hall of Famer Peachy Kellmeyer.

Way back in 1973, just after the WTA was born, Kellmeyer became its first tour director - which in large part meant handling everything. If it was hard to imagine having the perfect preparation for this job, that hardly fazed Kellmeyer. She'd been an excellent tennis player - in fact, the first woman ever to play Division I tennis on a men's team. She'd also been the primary plaintiff in a legal case that eventually opened the door for women in all sports to receive collegiate athletic scholarships. But most of all, Kellmeyer possessed a special balance - the ability to be both kind and tough. Said Evert, "She was so wonderful, so friendly, so warm."

A typical story involved King. Playing a tournament match, King was so disgusted by the quality of her play that she hit a ball out of the stadium. Then another. So surely more balls were needed, right? Wrong. A firm Kellmeyer told King: You lost those balls, play with what you've got. So it was that Billie Jean King finished the match playing with but one tennis ball.

Of course this was just one of thousands of examples of Kellmeyer's ability to think on her feet, best serve the game and remain a steadfast WTA employee through nine WTA CEOs.

As WTA CEO Stacey Allaster said about Kellmeyer, "It's always been about everyone else - and the sport. No one has given more."

Fitting enough, though, that once it was Kellmeyer's turn to speak she turned the spotlight back to her dear departed colleague.

Thurston, said Kellmeyer, had an incredible spirit, graced with her own kindness. Said Kellmeyer, "She showed that a big smile could go a long way, baby."

Joel Drucker has been covering tennis for more than 30 years. His work has appeared in a variety of print and broadcast media, including Tennis Channel, Tennis Magazine, USTA Magazine, CBS and HBO. He is also author of the book, Jimmy Connors Saved My Life.</Article>
    <Category>Tennis</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>SHARAPOVA ON SERENA: SHE'S THE BEST
Serena Williams' return to Indian Wells has been one of the most positive stories of the year - and her chief rival, World No.2 Maria Sharapova, is as excited as anyone.
Published March 14, 2015 12:14

Embed

INDIAN WELLS, CA, USA - Serena Williams' return to Indian Wells has been one of the most positive stories of the year so far, and while that may mean the rest of the field's chances of winning the BNP Paribas Open title are smaller now, their joy to have the World No.1 back here outweighs that.

And no player is more excited to have the World No.1 back than the World No.2, Maria Sharapova.

"I think it's all positive," Sharapova said in her All Access Hour interview this week.

"It's a great decision. It's great for the tour. It's great for tennis in general. I've always said that when you're playing any tournament, and especially being at the top of tennis, you want to be playing against the best. And as I've said before, she's the best. You want to be in the same field as the best."

Though it's been a while since Sharapova has beaten Williams, she's pushed many of their matches very close, including a very tight two-setter in the final of the Australian Open this past January.

She's got a lot of respect for her longtime rival - what does she admire the most about her?

"I admire the fact that even though she's achieved everything she has, that she still has the passion and desire to keep getting better," Sharapova said. "From a woman's perspective, at one point when you've achieved so much and you're so good at what you do, there's always an option or an easier way - but she's chosen the toughest way. It takes a lot of work and sacrifice to keep doing what we do."

Sharapova - like Williams a two-time champion at Indian Wells - will be playing for the first time since withdrawing before her semifinal match in Acapulco a few weeks ago due to a GI illness.

"It took a little bit longer than I expected to get better," Sharapova said. "I got home and had to take a little bit of time off. It was unfortunate. You never know when you're going to get that type of thing. But it was good to get rid of it, get my energy back and have a good week of training coming here."

And there was one more very important piece of business to discuss - how Dolce, her dog, is doing.

"I think he likes it here! He likes it better than the Miami humidity," Sharapova said.

"It's better for his hair here."</Article>
    <Category>Tennis</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Arsenal FC and Club Atlético de Madrid are both in arrears going into Tuesday's round of 16 second legs, but a quick look through the UEFA Champions League annals reveals that their situations are far from irretrievable. Even a 3-1 deficit can be surmounted by the away team, history has shown.

RELATED ITEMS
Tuesday night stats
Arsenal's knockout history
Bayern, Paris through
Madrid, Porto make it
Ronaldo sets goal record
Monaco v Arsenal preview
Monaco catch Arsenal cold
Atleti v Leverkusen preview
Leverkusen secure lead
Chelsea FC 3-1 FC Barcelona
FC Barcelona 5-1 Chelsea FC (aet)
1999/2000 quarter-finals
Pre-Roman Abramovich, Chelsea were not the European force they would become, and their first-leg triumph over Louis van Gaal's Barcelona – secured by a Gianfranco Zola effort and two in four minutes from Tore André Flo – marked an improbable success for Gianluca Vialli's men. They even came within seven minutes of winning the tie overall when Flo struck again in Catalonia to bring the second-leg score back to 2-1, only for Dani García to notch Barça's third. Rivaldo's penalty and a Patrick Kluivert goal finished off the Blues in extra time.

"It was the greatest night of my life," said Barcelona's Gabri García while team-mate Luís Figo concluded: "We played a perfect game. We had a big setback but managed to turn things around." A disappointed Vialli offered a mournful summary: "We did what we didn't want to do: defend badly."

AC Milan 4-1 RC Deportivo La Coruña
RC Deportivo La Coruña 4-0 AC Milan
2003/04 quarter-finals
Walter Pandiani put Deportivo in front at San Siro but that was long forgotten by full time, with Kaká scoring twice as Milan shredded their opponents. Ahead of the return fixture at the Riazor, Depor coach Javier Irureta was hanging onto little more than a dream. "This is of course a very complex, difficult and challenging task," he said. "But in football, miracles often happen, things you might not rationally expect."

Incredibly his side were ahead on aggregate by half-time in north-west Spain, Pandiani, Juan Carlos Valerón and Alberto Luque making it 3-0 – before substitute Fran González added a fourth goal on 76 minutes. Irureta duly promised to take the pilgrim trail to Santiago de Compostela, having prayed for success. "It is worth going to Santiago after this victory," he said. "I will do the walk to Santiago because a promise is a promise."

Real Madrid CF 4-2 AS Monaco FC
AS Monaco FC 3-1 Real Madrid CF
2003/04 quarter-finals
Whatever fairy dust had taken unfancied Monaco to the quarter-finals seemed to have blown away when the final whistle sounded at the Santiago Bernabéu on 24 March 2004. A four-goal post interval salvo from Madrid had sent the principality team into a tailspin, though Fernando Morientes's 83rd-minute strike for the visitors proved a lifeline. Coach Didier Deschamps was not about to admit defeat either, saying: "If I thought that, I'd be better off staying home."

A further goal down with seconds to go until half-time in the rematch, Deschamps might have been tempted to think again, but Ludovic Giuly levelled. Then Morientes – on loan from Madrid – headed a second and Giuly made it 3-1. The eventual away-goals victory might still have evaporated had Raúl González not fired a late chance over the bar. Morientes, meanwhile, was not sure whether to celebrate. "I'm very happy about Monaco's win," he said, "but I have friends in Madrid who must be having a difficult time."

©Getty Images
SSC Napoli 3-1 Chelsea FC
Chelsea FC 4-1 SSC Napoli (aet)
2011/12 round of 16
A change of manager provoked a startling fightback by Chelsea. André Villas-Boas's last European game with the London outfit ended in defeat in Naples; Juan Mata had given his team the initiative, but Ezequiel Lavezzi struck twice either side of an Edinson Cavani effort to leave the English club spiralling towards the exit. "There's a big possibility that, with this away goal, we can turn the tie around," Villas-Boas ventured afterwards.

The Portuguese, however, had been replaced by Roberto Di Matteo by the second leg, when goals from Didier Drogba, John Terry and Frank Lampard helped move the contest into extra time. Branislav Ivanović finally completed the Lazarus act after 105 minutes. "I've had some great nights but this will probably go down in club history," said Di Matteo, little knowing an even greater triumph in adversity would follow.

AC Milan 2-0 FC Barcelona
FC Barcelona 4-0 AC Milan
2012/13 round of 16
No side had ever recovered from a two-goal first-leg loss without the benefit of an away goal yet Barcelona made light of such unfavourable statistics amid a cacophony of enthusiastic support at Camp Nou. Lionel Messi's sublime first-half double wiped out Milan's lead and David Villa's goal early in the second period put the Blaugrana in control of the tie.

The home side still required some luck – at 1-0, M'Baye Niang hit the post – and they were not safe until Jordi Alba raced through to net a clinching fourth in stoppage time. Vanquished coach Massimiliano Allegri conceded Barça had played "extraordinarily well", while Lionel Messi told UEFA.com: "This is the Barça we and our fans want every game." They will need that Barcelona and more at home to Bayern.

Paris Saint-Germain 3-1 Chelsea FC
Chelsea FC 2-0 Paris Saint-Germain
2013/14 quarter-finals
Chelsea again! This time it was a José Mourinho-led team forced to play catch-up after a second-half David Luiz own goal followed by Javier Pastore's 93rd-minute coup de grace consigned them to a 3-1 setback in the French capital. As it transpired, though, Eden Hazard's earlier strike, from the penalty spot, would prove pivotal to the Londoners' revival.

Six days later André Schürrle came off the bench to make a 32nd-minute breakthrough in favour of the hosts. It was Schürrle's fellow substitute Demba Ba who sparked wild celebrations three minutes from full time by scooping home a direct Chelsea side's second to send them through on away goals. "We risked everything tonight," said Mourinho. "If, for some reason, we hadn't scored that second goal, we would still have been proud of the boys."</Article>
    <Category>Football</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Renascent Suárez is Barcelona's lethal weapon
Published: Monday 16 March 2015, 9.37CET
Manchester City FC have good reason to be quaking as they prepare to take on in-form FC Barcelona forward Luis Suárez, according to UEFA.com's Dúnia Martín
by Dúnia Martín
from Madrid

EMAIL
PRINT
Renascent Suárez is Barcelona's lethal weapon
Luis Suárez has struck a rich vein of form at Barcelona
©Getty Images

 
TRENDING NOW
1
Champions League quarter-final draw in depth
2
Champions League final tickets: Berlin 2015
3
UEFA.com's round of 16 team of the week
4
UEFA Champions League round of 16 by numbers
5
2015 final: Berlin
More
HEADLINES
Latest 
Team of the week
Round of 16 in numbers
Best of the second legs
Hunter on Barça-City
Download our podcast
More

 
So far, 2015 has been good to Luis Suárez. The Uruguayan has become one of FC Barcelona's outstanding performers, having rediscovered the goalscoring form that prompted the Catalan side to make the Liverpool FC man their record signing.

RELATED ITEMS
Best new signings
Suárez relaxed about City
Weekend review
Suárez earns Barça win
Suárez on City-Barcelona
Piqué reveals all
Last season: Barcelona 2-1 City
Date for last-eight draws
Rewind five months and things were not quite so rosy. Suárez made his Barça debut – his first outing after a three-month suspension – on 25 October against Real Madrid CF at the Santiago Bernabéu, but made a limited impact in a 3-1 defeat.

Coach Luis Enrique continued to support him, but Suárez's early months with Barça were not that remarkable in terms of statistics. He played 11 Blaugrana games in 2014, supplying six assists but scoring only three goals – decent figures but nothing compared to the 31-goal 2013/14 haul for Liverpool that earned him the ESM Golden Shoe, an honour he shared with Cristiano Ronaldo.

However, in retrospect it seems all the 27-year-old needed was a time to adapt. Since the turn of the year, the Barcelona striker has scored ten times and provided seven assists in all competitions. His two goals at Manchester City FC secured a 2-1 victory in the first leg of their UEFA Champions League last 16 tie, and his performance was rewarded with Man of the Match and UEFA.com Team of the Week honours.


Suárez's first Champions League memory
His eagerly-awaited return to England was an unequivocal triumph for the striker, who ignored the whistles from the home fans to score twice in the first half hour. "It is pleasing to help the team with important goals in a Champions League knockout game and of course to return to England and beat a team you're always motivated to face," said Suárez after the match. "Players like me get inspired when fans boo them – it helps motivate you a bit more."

There should be no boos at Camp Nou on Wednesday, with Suárez's goalscoring helping to signpost his contribution to the side more clearly. "Perhaps his work has been more spectacular and more appreciated by the public recently, but since he arrived I have noticed everything he has been doing for us," said Luis Enrique after the Uruguayan starred in a 3-1 win at Granada CF, scoring the opener and providing an assist. A week later he scored the first and last goal in an emphatic 6-1 defeat of Rayo Vallecano de Madrid, and on Saturday he helped his side see off a tough SD Eibar to win 2-0.

Without a doubt, Suárez is back to his best. Scoring goals, pressing the opposition and opening up gaps for his fellow forwards Lionel Messi and Neymar, with whom he has developed a terrific understanding. The only question that remains is how far that destructive attacking trident can take Barcelona this season?</Article>
    <Category>Football</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Club competition quarter-final draws on 20 March
Published: Friday 13 March 2015, 10.00CET
The UEFA Champions League and UEFA Europa League quarter-final draws will be made in Nyon next Friday, with media having until 19 March to apply for accreditation.

EMAIL
PRINT
Club competition quarter-final draws on 20 March
The quarter-final draw will be the next stop on the road to the UEFA Champions League final in Berlin
©Getty Images

 
TRENDING NOW
1
Champions League quarter-final draw in depth
2
Champions League final tickets: Berlin 2015
3
UEFA.com's round of 16 team of the week
4
UEFA Champions League round of 16 by numbers
5
2015 final: Berlin
More
HEADLINES
Latest 
Team of the week
Round of 16 in numbers
Best of the second legs
Hunter on Barça-City
Download our podcast
More

 
The draws for the quarter-finals of the 2014/15 UEFA club competitions will take place on Friday 20 March at UEFA's House of European Football in Nyon, Switzerland.

RELATED ITEMS
Bayern, Paris through
Ronaldo sets goal record
Madrid, Porto make it
Club Brugge's stance
West German dominance
Coaches' European revenges
The UEFA Champions League draw will be made from 12.00CET, carried out by UEFA General Secretary, Gianni Infantino, and UEFA's director of competitions, Giorgio Marchetti, assisted by the ambassador for the final in Berlin, Karl-Heinz Riedle.

The UEFA Europa League draw will follow at 13.00CET, conducted again by the UEFA General Secretary and the director of competitions, but assisted this time by the ambassador for the Warsaw final, Jerzy Dudek.

The quarter-final ties, involving the eight winners from the UEFA Champions League round of 16, will be determined in an open draw. At this stage of the competition, no teams are seeded and clubs from the same national association may be drawn against each other. The quarter-finals are played on a home-and-away basis, with the first legs on Tuesday 14 and Wednesday 15 April and the return legs a week later, on Tuesday 21 and Wednesday 22 April.

The same procedure will apply for the draw for the UEFA Europa League quarter-finals, which will be played on Thursday 16 April and Thursday 23 April.

Media representatives wishing to attend the quarter-final draws must apply by filling in the application form using the link http://uefa.to/1BwRdrR before midday on Thursday 19 March.

A live feed from the draw hall will be available in the media working area, which is also equipped with Wi-Fi connectivity. Both UEFA club competition draws will be broadcast live on UEFA.com and Eurosport.

The draws for the semi-finals of the UEFA Champions League and UEFA Europa League will be held on Friday 24 April at UEFA's Nyon HQ.</Article>
    <Category>Football</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Craigslist attack: Unborn child taken from pregnant woman
Police officer in Longmont, Colorado
A police officer on the scene of the stabbing in Longmont, Colorado
Colorado police say a woman stabbed a pregnant mother in the stomach and took her unborn child.

The victim, who was seven months pregnant, is likely to survive following surgery, but the baby died.

The pregnant woman was visiting the suspect's home to buy baby clothes that had been advertised on Craigslist.

Police said the suspect, Dynel Catrece Lane, took the baby to a hospital, where she claimed that she had a miscarriage.

Police have arrested Ms Lane, 34, on charges including first-degree murder, according to local media reports.

She did not know the victim, police said.

Police officers in Longmont, Colorado
Police say the suspect took the unborn child to the hospital and claimed to have had a miscarriage
Police command centre in Longmont, Colorado
Police say the two women did not know each other
According to the Daily Times-Call newspaper, police found the victim stabbed in the stomach on Wednesday at her home in Longmont, a small town north of Denver.

"She came by this house. She was attacked, and her baby was removed from her," Longmont Police Cdr Jeff Satur told the local newspaper.

Mr Satur said Ms Lane has two children of her own, and that her husband had driven her to the hospital before returning to the scene.

Ms Lane is expected to appear in court this afternoon.</Article>
    <Category>NoSport</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Australia's Norfolk Island to lose parliament, gain tax
Norfolk Island
Norfolk Island is one of Australia's most isolated territories
Residents on Australia's tiny Norfolk Island will lose their parliament and have to pay income tax under new government proposals.

The changes would also give the 1,800 islanders access to health and welfare payments for the first time.

The island - settled by the British six weeks after the First Fleet arrived in Sydney in 1788 - has struggled financially for years.

The opposition Labor Party is expected to support the proposals.

Halfway between New Caledonia and New Zealand, Norfolk Island is one of Australia's most geographically isolated and oldest territories.

The island is a popular tourism spot for Australians and New Zealanders but has a troubled history with the mainland.

In 1856, the descendants of Tahitians and the HMS Bounty mutineers resettled there from the Pitcairn Islands. Many of today's residents are direct descendants of the mutineers and have fiercely maintained their independence.

Under the proposed legislation, islanders would be required to pay taxes from 2016, including all personal and business taxes. They would not have to pay the 10% Goods and Services tax applied on the mainland.

Residents would also be entitled to access social security and health care payments, which they are currently denied.

Map
'Not sustainable'
The legislation to overhaul the territory's administration and finances would come before the federal parliament next week, said Assistant Minister for Infrastructure and Rural Development Jamie Briggs.

Mr Briggs said that under the current system the island was "simply not sustainable".

"They don't have the capacity to deliver the services," he told a press conference on Thursday.

"Asking a community of around 1,800 people to deliver federal functions such as immigration, quarantine and customs, social services and taxation, and state and local government services, is neither appropriate nor sustainable," he said.

"The reality is, infrastructure on Norfolk Island is run down, the health system not up to standard and many laws are out of date with all other Australian jurisdictions."

The island's economic situation has been the subject of a Royal Commission, 12 parliamentary enquiries and 20 commissioned expert reports, all of which recommended reforms.

Consultations with Norfolk Island residents revealed overwhelming support for reform, Mr Briggs said.

Grey line</Article>
    <Category>NoSport</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Litvinenko 'suspect' willing to co-operate with inquiry
Alexander Litvinenko
Continue reading the main story
Related Stories

Litvinenko inquiry shown CCTV footage
Litvinenko: Secrets begin to emerge
Timeline: Litvinenko death case
One of the suspects in the killing of the spy Alexander Litvinenko is thought to be willing to co-operate with the inquiry into his death, lawyers say.

The inquiry was told a man "who gave his name as Dmitri Kovtun", one of two men accused of killing the ex-Russian agent in London, had made contact.

Mr Litvinenko died of radioactive poisoning on 23 November 2006.

Mr Kovtun and Andrei Lugovoi have been named as suspects by police but both deny involvement and remain in Russia.

Mr Litvinenko is believed to have been given a fatal dose of polonium-210 in his tea during a meeting in a London hotel, on the first day of the month of his death.

The 43-year-old had been an officer with the Federal Security Service - the successor to the KGB - but fled to Britain where he became a UK citizen and fierce critic of the Kremlin.

Andrei Lugovoi, Dmitry Kovtun
Andrei Lugovoi and Dmitry Kovtun have both denied any involvement and remain in Russia
Counsel to the inquiry Robin Tam QC told chairman Sir Robert Owen: "During the course of the last fortnight, the solicitor to the inquiry has received communications from a man who has given his name as Dmitri Kovtun.

"He has said he is willing to take part in the inquiry."

He said it was not known if he intended to instruct legal representatives and there was no prospect of hearing any evidence from him before Easter.

'Unexpected development'
Sir Robert said: "It is highly regrettable that it is so late in the day that this approach and application from Dmitri Kovtun has been made."

Ben Emmerson, QC for Mr Litvinenko's widow Marina, said: "It is an unexpected development that Mr Kovtun should now seek to show his face, but if that's what he wants to do, then we would be more than happy to facilitate the opportunity to have a proper chance to question this man about his conduct and his role in the murder of Mr Litvinenko."

He added: "Should he be questioned by the police? There's an ongoing investigation in to his responsibility for the murder."

Richard Horwell, QC for the Metropolitan Police Commissioner, said: "We have grave concerns about what may be behind this development."

Sir Robert added: "Concerns that are shared by me."

He said however the inquiry decided to proceed, he would set strict time limits.

"This matter cannot be allowed to drift on, but I don't think there's anything more I can say now."</Article>
    <Category>NoSport</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>US drone kills al-Shabab leader in Somalia - Pentagon
Armed members of the militant group al-Shabab attend a rally on the outskirts of Mogadishu, Somalia in this February 2012 file photo. 
Al-Shabab militants have been driven out of the group's strongholds in Somalia
Continue reading the main story
Somalia: Failed State

Poet jihadist
‘Mosquito militants’
Al-Shabab profile
Who are al-Shabab? Watch
The US defence department has confirmed that it has killed an al-Shabab leader, Adan Garar.

The Pentagon says the militant was hit by a drone equipped with Hellfire missiles in southern Somalia last Friday.

Garar was a suspect in the 2013 Westgate Mall attack in Nairobi that left 67 people dead.

The US believes Garar was overseeing operations that "target US persons and other Western interests".

He was a member of the security and intelligence wing and a "key operative responsible for coordinating al-Shabab's external operations", according to the Pentagon.

The operation took place about 150 miles (240km) west of Mogadishu near the town of Dinsoor.

Soldiers and armed police hunt gunmen who went on a shooting spree in Westgate shopping centre in Nairobi 21 September 2013. 
Garar is accused of planning the 2013 Westgate Mall attack in Nairobi that killed 67 people
Washington has supported an African Union (AU) force, which has driven the fundamentalist group from strongholds across Somalia since 2011.

The US defence department said in a statement that Garar's death "has dealt another significant blow to the al-Shabab terrorist organisation in Somalia".

Hours before the Pentagon confirmed the news, an al-Shabab attack killed four in north-east Kenya.

The militant group has vowed to punish Kenya for its role in the AU force.</Article>
    <Category>NoSport</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Inside the matchup: Rangers vs. Capitals
Wednesday, 03.11.2015 / 10:40 AM / Tale of the Tape
By John Kreiser - NHL.com Managing Editor
CommentPrintE-mail
The New York Rangers can take over first place in the Metropolitan Division by defeating the Washington Capitals in the Wednesday Night Rivalry game (8 p.m. ET; NBCSN, SN1, TVA Sports).

The Rangers will be playing the second half of a back-to-back after edging the first-place New York Islanders 2-1 on Tuesday, a victory that moved them within one point of the division lead with four games in hand. The Capitals are well-rested; they've been off since defeating the Buffalo Sabres 6-1 on Saturday.

Though the season is past the three-quarters mark, this is New York's first visit to Washington and the second game between the Rangers and Capitals. They'll play at Madison Square Garden on March 29 and end the season against each other at Verizon Center on April 11.</Article>
    <Category>IceHockey</Category>
    <IsProcessed>false</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Jazz trade former No. 3 pick Kanter to Thunder
By KAREEM COPELAND | Associated Press 
POSTED: Feb 19, 2015 8:13 PM ET

AD
SALT LAKE CITY (AP) — A person familiar with the situation says the Utah Jazz have traded Enes Kanter to the Oklahoma City Thunder for fellow center Kendrick Perkins.
The person spoke Thursday on condition of anonymity because the teams had not announced the move. There likely will be more players and draft picks involved when the trade is finalized.
Kanter, the No. 3 overall pick in the 2011 draft, said last week that he wanted to be traded. The Turkish center was unhappy that his minutes had fluctuated in a front-court rotation with Rudy Gobert, Derrick Favors and Trevor Booker.
Kanter, 22, is averaging 13.8 points, 7.8 rebounds and 27.1 minutes this season. He is eligible for restricted free agency after the season.
Perkins is a 12-year veteran in the final year of a five-year deal. He is averaging 4.0 and 5.5 rebounds in 19.2 minutes per game. </Article>
    <Category>Basketball</Category>
    <IsProcessed>false</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>SERENA ON INDIAN WELLS: IT WAS TIME
Serena Williams met the press at the BNP Paribas Open for the first time in 14 years on Thursday. What did the World No.1 say? Watch the full press conference here.
Published March 12, 2015 12:15

Embed

INDIAN WELLS, CA, USA - Serena Williams met the media in a very deep pre-tournament press conference at the BNP Paribas Open on Thursday, and the No.1 topic she was asked about was her return. Not her return of serve, though it's one of the best in the business - her return to Indian Wells.

"It was just a really good opportunity for me. It was time," Williams said. "There wasn't one thing that said I should come back in 2015 - I didn't even know I'd still be playing this year.

"It was more or less just time. I just kind of felt it."

Williams is playing the BNP Paribas Open for the first time since 2001, when she battled through some very controversial circumstances in the final for her second title in three years at the tournament.

And after 14 years, Williams has forgiven and is ready for another run at the title.

"I was taught when I was young to always forgive, and always try to look at the bigger picture, so to say," Williams commented. "In order to forgive you have to be ready to let go of everything. I kind of let go a long time ago, but I still wasn't at the point where I was ready to come back to Indian Wells. I think I was a little nervous as well. So trying to get over those nerves of coming back and how I feel, and thinking about what it's going to be like - you have to let a lot of those emotions go."

Williams will open her tournament against on Friday night against Monica Niculescu, a crafty veteran who has been playing on the tour for many years - the two have never played each other though.

The World No.1 was asked about returning to center court and the emotions that could come with it.

"I'm not here to focus on what happened in 2001," she said. "I'm looking forward to stepping out on center court and letting the whole world know that it doesn't matter about something that wasn't right, or something that hurt you and hurt your family. You can come out and be strong and say, 'I'm still going to be here, I'm still going to survive and I'm still going to be the best person that I can be.'"

And what about sister and fellow WTA legend Venus Williams, who opted to not return this year?

"If she didn't support me I wouldn't be here," she said.

"She 100% supports me and is very happy I'm here - she even encouraged me to come."

Wherever Williams goes she's the favorite for the title. She's been ranked No.1 in the world for more than two years running, after all. She could cross back into a new level of domination with a strong showing here, too - if she wins the title, or even reaches the final, she'll surpass 10,000 points on the WTA Rankings, a threshold she hasn't crossed since the French Open fortnight last year.

But she's only focused on one thing: "I'm not putting any pressure on myself here at all. I haven't played a WTA event since Australia, so I'm just coming in here trying to do the best I can do."</Article>
    <Category>Tennis</Category>
    <IsProcessed>false</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Borussia Dortmund striker Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang discusses hip hop, movies, the joys of playing with Marco Reus and that superhero celebration in a live Facebook Q&amp;A.

EMAIL
PRINT
Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang: the lowdown
Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang celebrates his goal against Wolfsburg
©Getty Images

 
TRENDING NOW
1
Champions League quarter-final draw in depth
2
Champions League final tickets: Berlin 2015
3
UEFA.com's round of 16 team of the week
4
UEFA Champions League round of 16 by numbers
5
2015 final: Berlin
More
HEADLINES
Latest 
Team of the week
Round of 16 in numbers
Best of the second legs
Hunter on Barça-City
Download our podcast
More

 
Marco Reus, favourite films and superhero celebrations were on the agenda when Borussia Dortmund forward Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang took part in a live Q&amp;A on the UEFA Champions League Facebook page.


Favourite movie?

Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang: Inception.

Why the superhero celebration?

Aubameyang: I've always liked comics. It's a reminder that even though it's our job, football remains a show for people to enjoy.

What is it like playing with Reus?

Aubameyang: You need to be prepared and strong because he's both of those things. You also need to play at your highest level because someone like Reus is so quick and clever.

Favourite player ever?

Aubameyang: The Brazilian Ronaldo.

One player you would like Dortmund to sign?

Aubameyang: Neymar.

What music do you like listening to before a match?

Aubameyang: Usually I put the music on in the dressing room! I like hip hop and old school music.

What are the Dortmund fans like?

Aubameyang: They are amazing. The best in Europe. They're always there for us and follow us in big numbers wherever we play.

Favourite food?

Aubameyang: The crepes that my mum makes!


How fast can you run 100 metres?

Aubameyang: I don't know exactly. I've never timed myself with a stopwatch. My coach in France said I could do 100 metres in ten seconds and something.

What is it like working with Jürgen Klopp?

Aubameyang: It's easy in the end. It's about watching and learning, and then it's up to you. There are so many great players here and it's a great club. I've been here a while now and I know very well how hard they work.

Advice for an aspiring footballer?

Aubameyang: To work hard at school because it's not always easy to break through. When you've decided what you want to do, you have to commit to it, make a lot of sacrifices. You may have to go it alone without your parents. </Article>
    <Category>Football</Category>
    <IsProcessed>false</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Afghan woman lynched in Kabul 'after burning Koran'
Afghan men feed pigeons in front of the Shad-u-Shamshera Walisaib mosque, in Kabul, 11 September 2005.
The woman was killed near the Shah-Du-Shamshaira mosque in Kabul
Continue reading the main story
Related Stories

Has life improved for Afghan women?
Afghanistan country profile
A mob in Afghanistan's capital Kabul has lynched a woman after she allegedly burned a copy of the Koran near a mosque, police say.

Local police commander Saleh Mohammad told the BBC she was killed when "hundreds of locals and passersby attacked her with stones and sticks".

Witnesses say her body was then set on fire. Four suspects have been arrested but the woman has not been identified.

The killing is thought to be the first incident of its kind in Afghanistan.

However, correspondents say it is fairly common in neighbouring Pakistan.

One eyewitness told the BBC how the lynching was carried out near the Shah-Du-Shamshaira mosque and shrine.

"I heard noise, I went and people said that a woman is burning Koran. When I went closer I saw angry people shouting they want to kill the woman.

"They beat her to death and then threw her on the river side and burned her. Firefighters later came and put out the fire and took the body."

Interior ministry spokesman Sediq Seddiqi said officials were not sure exactly what caused the incident.

Afghan's Tolo news agency said quoted the parents of the woman, named only as Farkhunda, as saying she had suffered from a mental illness for 16 years.

The parents, who were not named, told Tolo she had not intentionally burnt the Koran.</Article>
    <Category>NoSport</Category>
    <IsProcessed>false</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
</ArrayOfLabeledArticle>