<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ArrayOfLabeledArticle xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Veronika Petra-Goodnight was working as a financial assistant at a university when she first fell in love with hula hooping.

She was enchanted by a performer’s tricks, twists and turns and decided to try it at home. Within the first month, Petra-Goodnight hula hooped so frequently that it gave her a hernia.

She pressed on, challenging herself with new tricks, including twirling a hoop engulfed in flames. She began teaching workshops as she advanced her craft. After getting voted fire hooper of the year by online group Hooping.org, Petra-Goodnight started receiving phone calls from talent agencies.

More attention — and success — followed. She appeared in Britney Spears’ Circus music video, she travelled to Beirut with Cirque USA and went to London with Cirque Du Soleil.

 “When I resigned my job, I left a note that read, ‘I am quitting to run away with the circus,’ then I ate fire at my going-away party,” said Petra-Goodnight, who has been performing as a profession since 2007.

It might sound glamorous — and for some it is. But behind the scenes, the circus business isn’t always as exciting as tumbling across elephants in feather headdresses, juggling on a unicycle or swinging across the sky on a mile-high trapeze.

Some performers say they have made tough lifestyle choices: leaving a marriage, forgoing health insurance despite high risk of major injury and living out of tiny trailers in venue parking lots.

Still, those who have run away with the circus say the adrenaline rush of a post-performance standing ovation, the chance to travel the world and family-like relationships with everyone (and everything) from contortionists to zebras can make it worthwhile.

Navigating the ropes

The path of a circus performer is often similar to that of a touring theatre actor’s career. In other words, it’s tough. There are the dynamics of life on the road, fierce competition to secure limited and temporary contracts, constant self-promotion and auditions before directors who seem to specialise in harsh opinions. Added to that, Petra-Goodnight and others say, performers must be physically fit at all times. They must also continually sharpen and enhance their skills to remain competitive, especially if they didn’t go to circus school.

Rex Camphuis, co-founding executive director of Cirque School LA said he estimates about 50% of performers go to a specialised circus school, where training lasts two to four years and a bachelor’s degree in circus arts is attainable. In Australia, for instance, a degree might cost $13,000 for locals ($10,000) and $21,550 ($16,578) for international students, according to the National Institute of Circus Arts Australia. But schooling alone doesn’t necessarily land you a circus job, since producers don’t typically care about credentials. Instead, they focus on auditions.

 “You have to find time to train, to feed your body right, to tune your performances and make sure they’re appropriate for who has hired you, and at the same time, maintain who you are and your personal life,” Petra-Goodnight said.

And you’ll be doing it on a limited budget. The circus life doesn’t exactly pay well for most.

Glam life, unglamorous pay

Camphuis estimates a performer can make anywhere from $200 to $3,500 for a single performance. Rates, he said, can drop to $50 to $250 per show if someone performs every day while on tour. And pay varies wildly from year to year. Petra-Goodnight said she could make $10,000 in a month, then not make more than $10, 000 in a year.

Expenses also add up.

Frequent travel may be fun, but performers often pay their own way. In many cases, they must also supply their own equipment and costumes.

Rebecca Ostroff, 58, who dangles by her teeth and spins from a swinging apparatus for US-based Kelly Miller Circus might spend $300 on rhinestones for a costume and the same for a headdress. She also goes through about several cases of dental floss per year, which she uses to re-sew jewels onto her costumes that fall off during vigorous use.

Having health insurance is also a necessary expense, especially since an injury or poor health could cost you your career. In 2014, tumbler and trapeze artist Jeannemarie Van Zeyl tore her rotator cuff during a trapeze act and she hasn’t returned to performing. She’s also suffered concussions. Many performers say injuries come with the territory, especially when they create new, limit-pushing acts.

Securing work

Many performers develop an original act with extreme feats like juggling chainsaws or maybe an unusual twist like training goats to jump through hoops. The act generates buzz and interest, making it easier to land gigs through word of mouth.

For instance, Ostroff’s “Iron Jaw” act won her a performance in the 2011 circus film Water for Elephants. Ostroff said she has performed her routine about 500 times a year for the last 27 years and has also worked as a ringmaster.

While less common, some acts are represented by agencies such as the international Circus Stardust Entertainment, said Jack Marsh, creative director of American Circus Flora. Other times, acts are scouted, much like professional athletes.

Marsh said he frequents shows and festivals, including the Montreal Completement Cirque, to scout acts from places as diverse as Cuba, Kazakhstan and Finland. He also receives upwards of 200 videos a year from prospective performers.

Some big-name circuses such as Cirque du Soleil post job opportunities on their websites, while other circuses, including Ringling Brothers Barnum and Bailey, post listings on popular job boards like Careerbuilder.com.

Acts get locked in by a circus well in advance, especially if the performer doesn’t have a work visa in the production’s native country.

Out of balance

The stress of circus life can be a difficult balance for someone who wants a home and family.

While Van Zeyl loves circus performance, she also craves the normalcy of everyday life.

“If you want to be full-fledged, you have to be completely devoted — not have a cat, own a house, or be in love,” said Van Zeyl. “But I have a mortgage to pay and got married a year ago. I think those are things you have to weigh out.”

She has made trade-offs to create work-life balance, including performing in small, local productions and rounding out her income by teaching tumbling. It helps that she lives about 100km outside of Los Angeles: a hub for music video and television gigs that can be had through recruitment agencies like LA Circus that cast performers locally.

Meanwhile Ostroff, whose husband is a trumpet player in the circus band, home schools her daughter while on the road and argues circus life isn’t all that different than life in any two-income home.

“It’s just like you live in a town and you have your house and your job or school and you do your things except you’re in a circus, so your house just happens to change locations,” Ostroff said.

Regardless, most performers say they wouldn’t trade circus life for workaday. When Petra-Goodnight thinks she’s seen it all, over and over again she is surprised. Recently, she went to a Cirque Dreams performance where she saw a Romanian family perform a jaw-dropping tumbling act and an Armenian couple do contortionist moves while spinning on roller skates.

“I thought, at any second he could lose her hand and she would go flying. When you see those type of circus performers, it’s mindboggling,” Petra-Goodnight said. “Then you see something in [audience members] spark when they go to shows like this and it is so cool to witness.”</Article>
    <Category>NoSport</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Kompany: Huge difference between City and Barça, Bayern
(PA) Thursday 19 March 2015
Share
2
Kompany: Huge difference between City and Barça, Bayern
© Getty Images
Manchester City captain Vincent Kompany accepts the club still remain a long way short of fulfilling their European dreams. The gap between City and the continent's best clubs was starkly illustrated on Wednesday, when Barcelona dumped the English champions out of the UEFA Champions League with a commanding performance at Camp Nou.

Thanks to the brilliance of Joe Hart, City at least kept the scoreline respectable - losing 1-0 for a 3-1 aggregate defeat - but they were distinctly second best to a Barça side inspired by the magnificent Lionel Messi. City may have made considerable progress in the seven years since their Abu Dhabi takeover, but the journey still has a long way to go.

Kompany said: "The reality is they were a better team, there is no shame in admitting that. For me there is a big, big difference. I will just mention Bayern Munich and Barcelona, and then there are the rest of the teams, with Real Madrid probably in between.

"Ultimately we have always said our goal is to become as good as them, but it will take some time. They are really good.

"Bayern Munich and Barcelona are not just Champions League-winning teams, they are World Cup-winning teams as well. They have generations that have played together a long time.

"Of course we want to make up the gap but you just have to be true to yourself. We have the ambition to be as good as they are one day, but it is not going to happen overnight."

There is a big, big difference. I will just mention Bayern Munich and Barcelona, and then there are the rest of the teams, with Real Madrid probably in between.Vincent Kompany
City's exit meant that England will not have a representative in the quarter-finals of the Champions League for the second time in three seasons.

"The gap will eventually get closer," said Kompany. "Whether it is Arsenal, Chelsea, [Manchester] United, the gap will become closer and I just hope it is us that gets there the first."

'Phenomenal' Hart
City were outplayed in the first leg at the Etihad Stadium three weeks ago, but had hoped Hart's late penalty save, which kept the score 2-1, might have proved the tie's turning point. It proved anything but as Barcelona dominated from the outset, hitting the post within moments through Neymar. Messi was at his inspirational best, setting up Ivan Rakitic's 31st-minute goal and generally running City ragged.

It was remarkable the scoreline stayed at 1-0, with Luis Suarez also hitting the woodwork twice and England goalkeeper Hart producing a series of stunning saves in one of the best performances of his career. City might have made the latter stages interesting had Sergio Aguero not had a penalty saved by Marc-Andre ter Stegen, but they could complain little about the result.

Asked about Hart's display, Kompany said: "It was phenomenal. On that side of the pitch I felt we had all the luck we needed to get a result.

"It was probably just the penalty - if we had scored a goal it could have been a different game. It would have been a great way to get back into the tie, and it would have been interesting to see what the last 15 minutes would have been like back at 1-1.

"If you want to win against those teams you need a very special performance and a little bit of luck on your side. Then you can beat them, but every team can lose. There is no shame."

Kompany demands strong finish
Despite progress always seeming unlikely, the defeat is another blow to City's morale after an indifferent spell in the Premier League. Having fallen six points behind Chelsea, who have a game in hand, it now seems unlikely City can retain their title and their season is in danger of fizzling out. They could even face a battle to hold on to second place as the likes of Arsenal, Liverpool and Manchester United gear up for a strong finish. Kompany is determined to ensure that does not happen.

The 28-year-old said: "Forget about Chelsea. We owe it to ourselves, to our fans to have a good end to this campaign. Then again, if we finish this campaign as good as we can, maybe there is still something in it. We will have to see. It is not in our hands by any means, but we just have to go back and work hard and improve."</Article>
    <Category>Football</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>MARIA SHARAPOVA: DRIVEN TO SUCCEED
Maria Sharapova has crammed a lot into her time as Porsche brand ambassador, juggling her tennis commitments with advertising shoots, car design and chauffer-driven rides with Formula 1 drivers.
Published March 18, 2015 12:12

Maria Sharapova: Driven To Succeed Maria Sharapova
Two years ago, Maria Sharapova added German sports car manufacturer Porsche to her ever-growing list of endorsement contracts.

Porsche hand-picked Sharapova to head up its global communications campaign, and she has thrown herself into the role with gusto. The Russian has crammed a lot into her time as brand ambassador, juggling her tennis globe-trotting with advertising shoots, car design and chauffeur-driven rides with Formula 1 drivers.

In a blog for luxury lifestyle publication Haute Living, Sharapova looks back on her favorite moments from an action-packed journey, which begin, aptly enough, at the Porsche Tennis Grand Prix in Stuttgart. The Russian was no stranger to the automobile behemoth, having taken home a 911 Carrera S Cabriolet after winning the previous year's tournament, and to the delight of all parties - save for beaten finalist Li Na - she defended her title in style.

Porsche's long-term relationship with tennis has made it an ideal fit in the Sharapova sponsorship portfolio, and she has used the ambassadorial platform to not only promote the sport but also the modern woman.

"One of the things I've loved most is the opportunity to help Porsche expand its brand message to women - sports cars aren't just for men! I jumped at the chance to represent the modern woman: a woman with a successful career and a myriad of passions, a woman who treats herself to luxury, and most of all, a woman who likes to drive her own life," Sharapova told Haute Living readers.

There have also been plenty of perks to the gig. One such moment came at last year's Winter Olympics in the Russian's hometown of Sochi, where she unveiled a car with a difference: The Panamera GTS 'by Maria Sharapova'.</Article>
    <Category>Tennis</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
  <LabeledArticle>
    <Article>Five things to watch when Blackhawks face Rangers
Wednesday, 03.18.2015 / 3:00 AM / NHL Insider
By Brian Compton - NHL.com Deputy Managing Editor
CommentPrintE-mail
It may very well be a preview of the Stanley Cup Final when the New York Rangers host the Chicago Blackhawks at Madison Square Garden. This week's Wednesday Night Rivalry game (8 p.m. ET; NBCSN, TVA, SN1) features two of the top teams in the NHL, each of which seems primed to play deep into the spring.

With the Rangers atop the League standings and the Blackhawks battling for position in the Central Division, there's plenty at stake for each team.

Here are five things to watch between the Rangers and Blackhawks:


WEDNESDAY NIGHT RIVALRY
The Chicago Blackhawks visit the New York Rangers at 8 p.m. ET in the early game of a Wednesday Night Rivalry doubleheader. In the late game, the Los Angeles Kings continue their playoff push against the Anaheim Ducks at 10:30 p.m. ET.
Hawks vs. Rangers video | Kings vs. Ducks video
X-Factors: Saad, Talbot video | Toffoli, Lindholm video
Hawks-Rangers storylines | Tale of the Tape
Closer look: CHI, NYR play fast | Weekes
Richards eyes Cup | Lundqvist injury update
Kopitar, Gabby want more | Williams on push
video Join the Twitter conversation: #RivalryNight
1. Who replaces St. Louis?
The Rangers recently lost defenseman Kevin Klein for 3-4 weeks because of an upper-body injury, and now they'll be without forward Martin St. Louis, who sustained a lower-body injury late in a 2-1 win against the Florida Panthers on Sunday.

St. Louis, who has 47 points (20 goals, 27 assists) in 68 games, is expected to miss 10-14 days.

Rangers left wing Tanner Glass missed the game Sunday because of upper-body soreness, but is expected to play against the Blackhawks. That would give New York 12 healthy forwards.

2. Blackhawks' power play clicking again

Prior to its back-to-back road wins, Chicago struggled with the man-advantage, going 1-for-16 in its previous six games. But the Blackhawks scored four power-play goals in 11 opportunities in wins against the Arizona Coyotes and San Jose Sharks. Defenseman Duncan Keith and forward Patrick Sharp scored on the power play against the Sharks on Saturday.

"It's nice to have some relief across the board in those areas definitely," Sharp, who ended a 19-game goal drought, told the Blackhawks website. "Power play, penalty kill … those things are going to be up and down all season long. You try to make them as consistent as possible, but there's certainly peaks and valleys. We can gain some confidence knowing that we scored a couple of goals on the power play in both games and we know how valuable both specials teams are going to be going down the stretch."

3. All eyes on Talbot

Rangers fans probably would have settled for .500 hockey when they learned No. 1 goalie Henrik Lundqvist would miss a substantial amount of time because of a vascular injury. But New York hasn't missed a beat thanks to the play of Cam Talbot.

Talbot was named the NHL's Second Star of the week on Monday after going 3-0-0 with a 1.00 GAA and a .969 save percentage, helping the Rangers extend their win streak to five games. Talbot made 38 saves in a 2-1 victory against the Florida Panthers on Sunday.

"It didn't surprise anybody in here, to be honest," Rangers defenseman Marc Staal said. "Obviously you don't want to see what happened to [Lundqvist] happen, but we're excited for him to get an opportunity to show what he's got on a consistent basis. He's been very good for us as a backup. It's his time to shine."

Lundqvist was cleared to practice on Tuesday, which means the number of starts Talbot receives down the stretch will likely decrease dramatically. But there's no denying how much he's meant to the Rangers during the past six weeks.

4. Who's in goal for Blackhawks?


Scott Darling

SCOTT DARLING
GOALIE - CHI
RECORD: 6-3-0
GAA: 2.18 | SVP: .930
Chicago coach Joel Quenneville opted to start No. 1 goalie Corey Crawford against the New York Islanders at United Center on Tuesday. Will Crawford will play against the Rangers with such a quick turnaround.
If Crawford does not play, the Blackhawks would start Scott Darling, who has a 2.18 GAA and a .930 save percentage in nine games with Chicago this season.

"Big games, we'll see," Quenneville said.

Quenneville added it would be "under discussion" regarding starting Crawford again Wednesday.

5. Rangers shuffle lines

New York's top line will have a different look against the Blackhawks. Seeking more production from some of his top forwards (especially while St. Louis is out), Rangers coach Alain Vigneault reunited center Derek Stepan and wings Chris Kreider and Rick Nash. Stepan does not have a point in the past 10 games; Kreider has gone six games without a goal and Nash, who has 39 goals, has one goal in his past six.

Center Derick Brassard is expected to play with Kevin Hayes on the left and Mats Zuccarello on the right.

"I play with Rick on the penalty kill, and when I am out there with him, my job is to try to create space for him, for situations in which he can get a 1-on-1 situation or maybe challenge somebody and use his big body to get the puck to the net," Stepan said, according to the Daily News. "He shoots the puck too. If you look at his stats, I think he has 200 and some odd shots (260). He's a shooter.

"So it's important you understand that when he does have the puck to support him … and communicate with him. Because if he gives you the puck and you are able to give it back to him, he's going to be able to create space."</Article>
    <Category>IceHockey</Category>
    <IsProcessed>true</IsProcessed>
  </LabeledArticle>
</ArrayOfLabeledArticle>